round and round we Go losing
round and round we Go losing
self I keep Tell Myself but I Don't Let
self I keep Tell Myself but I Don't Let
You
You
know this What
know this What
we str on r
we str on
for all
for all
Those find
Those find
a
a
[Music]
[Música]
Under your
Under your
spot
spot
surv Under your
surv Under your
Spotlight That's the way Every goes
Spotlight That's the way Every goes
Looking Back I know we Start falling we
Looking Back I know we Start falling we
were
were
falling
falling
[Music]
[Música]
yeah my heart off was a feeling Never
yeah my heart off was a feeling Never
Enough for you baby when you left me Chasing
Enough for you baby when you left me
you Chasing
Chasing you Chasing
you try to find a
you try to find a
we can
we can
be all
be all
Those by Under
Those
your
by Under your
[Music]
[Música]
SP
SP
and
and
[Music]
[Música]
God forgive Me I've been without Again I've
God forgive Me I've been sin Again I've
abandoned my Friends When call my phone
abandoned my Friends When call my phone
I press the Again says Don't be Alone I
I press the Again says Don't be Alone I
am says You're sick I am I'm Whatever
am says You're sick I am I'm Whatever
that you say I am Whatever that you say I [Music] am
that you say I
Whatever that you say am say I'm Dead
am Whatever that you say am say I'm Dead
on the
on the
inside I'm feeling Dead on the I don't need
inside I'm feeling Dead on
Any inside
the I don't need Any
so please baby Shut  your
inside so please baby Shut your
Mouth I've been Dancing  with the thought
Mouth I've been Dancing with the thought
of
of
losing
losing
los so say what you want say what you
los so say what you want say what you
can I'm Whatever that you say I
can I'm Whatever that you say I
am Whatever that
am
you say I [
Whatever that you say I
Music]
[Música]
am Whatever that you my addiction Just
am Whatever that you my addiction Just
Another vic of people try to Tell me Who I am Who
Another vic of people try to Tell me Who
procrastination mo I don't even have a [
procrastination mo I don't even have
Music]
[Música]
Whatever that
Whatever that
you Whatever that you say
you Whatever that you say
am Whatever that you
am Whatever that you
say I'm Whatever that you say I
say I'm Whatever that you say I
am
am
It's not my fault you know I Had to Walk a It
It's not my fault you know I Had to Walk
's been years and One of Us has ch we say we trying but we Just Stay the same and the Truth is I think me Myself and I least give it a
a It's been years and One of Us has ch
[Music]
[Música]
Truth me Myself And I at  at least give it a [Music
Truth me Myself And I at least give it a
try we Our [Music
try we Our
] and me Myself
[Música]
And I at Give a [Music
me Myself And I at Give a
]
[Música]
try see Tonight see
try see Tonight
Love see t see [Music
Love see t see
]
[Música]
Myself
Myself
and Give a
and Give a
TR
TR
[Music]
[Música]
Good
Buenas
night good night What's up
noches buenas noches Qué
What were
pasa Qué
you drinking let's see I'm going to see the members let's
bebías a ver voy a ver los miembros a
see how they're doing br what
ver cómo siguen br qué
's up let's see I'm going to see the members see
pasa a ver voy a ver los miembros a ver
if they fit in with what we had with
si cuadran con lo que teníamos que con
what we had before the long weekend no let's
lo que teníamos antes del puente no a
see if they've done too much for us during the long
ver si nos han ido mucho durante el
weekend What's up What's up
puente Qué
[ __ ] almost 2 in the morning I
pasa [__] casi las 2 de la mañana
'm exhausted eh
estoy reventado eh
family I'm tired this but I'm going to
familia estoy cansad este pero voy a
be here with you talking about some
estar aquí con ustedes comentando unas
things already screwed me the covid Well let's see I understand that
cosillas ya me jod el covid Pues a ver
yes I understand that yes What happens yes it
sí entiendo que sí Lo que pasa que sí
's true that like I've lost
que es verdad que como que he perdido
a lot of lung capacity it's hard for
mucha capacidad pulmonar me cuesta
me it's a little bit eh breathe and
mucho me cuesta un poquete eh respirar y
that eh Let's
eso eh A
see it's hard for me to breathe and
ver me cuesta un po respirar y
other
demás
members say no kidding we call him
miembros dice fuera de joda le decimos
grandpa but I don't have The stamina that he
abuelo pero yo no tengo El aguante que
has  he endured a 6 hour trip a
tiene él se bancó un viaje de 6 horas un
direct in the
directo en la
señoreros Thanks for recognizing it
señoreros Gracias por reconocerlo
2464 well come on let's touch it a little
2464 bueno venga vamos a tocarlo un poco
come on let's put it
venga vamos a ponerlo
right how the hell have the members gone up
bien cómo [__] han subido los miembros
while we weren't
mientras que no
there how is it possible that the members go up
estbamos cómo es posible que suban los
while we're not there let's
miembros mientras que no
see let's see the ones from telesalseo I have
ver vamos a ver los de los de telesalseo
n't looked at them I'll look at them
No los he mirado los miro
tomorrow the ones from telesalseo I haven't looked at it coastal coastal
mañana los de telesalseo no lo he mirado
factors total eh
litoral litoral factores total eh
factors total 6 hours man I came
factores total 6 horas tío Es que vengo
from the other end of the Peninsula eh
desde la otra punta de la Península eh
Like who
Como quién
says literally 6 hours
dice literalmente 6 horas
eh And yesterday I was Yesterday I was in Vigo man
eh Y ayer estuve Ayer estuve en vigo tío
all this with my car eh all this with
todo esto con mi coche eh todo esto con
my car
mi coche
dude they dedicated a thread to you not a
chaval te dedicaron un hilo no un hilo
matt thread I don't know anymore I don't even know
mat yo no sé ya yo no sé ya ni ni
how many things they dedicate to me a day what
cuántas cosas me dedican al día a qué
thread are you referring to this time they
hilo te refieres en esta ocasión te
dedicated a thread to you but he tells me he
dedicaron un hilo a pero me lo dice me
tells me as if yes Ah of course that thread not the one they
lo dice como sí Ah claro ese hilo no el
dedicated to me no Of course tomorrow I'll
que me dedicaron no Claro claro mañana
answer him my god But my son if it's that
le contesto madre mía Pero hijo mío si
luckily Ah but  wait of course Wait wait I have to
es que por suerte Ah pero espérate
play
claro Espérate Espérate tengo que tocar
this let's play it let's play it Ah
esto vamos a tocarlo vamos a tocarlo Ah
look they dedicated a thread to me it's like if you
mira me dedicaron un hilo es como si me
tell me they dedicated a live to you eh they
dices te dedicaron un directo eh te
dedicated a live to you
dedicaron un directo
Sure that live Yes yes it was good that one that
Claro ese directo Sí sí estuvo bueno ese
only live that they dedicated to me that
ese único directo que me dedicaron al
day was very good let's see let's see let's
día estuvo muy bueno a ver vamos a ver
see
vamos a ver
members Javi the
miembros Javi el
little one son go on if I cared about the
canijo hijo anda que si me importara los
threads and the videos and the live shows that they
hilos y los vídeos y los directos que me
dedicate to me if I had to get angry
dedican si me tuviera que enfadar
eh for each video each thread each t each
eh por cada vídeo cada hilo cada t cada
Twitter account that they dedicate to
cuenta de Twitter que me dedican no
me I never end the anger I don't care if they
acabo con los enfados a mí me da igual
dedicate whatever they want to me it's very
que me dediquen lo que quieran está mu
good that I also curse the people I want
bien eso yo también me cago en la gente
when I feel like it
que me da la gana cuando me da la gana
curse that's it without
cagarme ya está sin
further ado better say when they don't dedicate threads
más mejor di cuando no le dedican hilos
and live shows and we finish before let's see threads
y directos y acabamos antes a ver hilos
during the long weekend I have seen a lot of
durante el puente he visto un montón de
threads but it's that I have seen I have seen
hilos pero es que he visto a he visto
because you send it all to me I mean I'm not
porque me lo mandáis todo o sea no os
going to lie to you and I go say Ah I have not
voy a engañar y voy decí Ah yo no he
seen I have not seen I am very important
visto no he visto yo soy muy importante
and no  I see nothing of what they tell me I have
y no veo nada de lo que me dicen he
seen I have seen threads that have been dedicated to me
visto he visto hilos que me han dedicado
Of course I have seen threads I have seen things I have seen I have
Claro que he visto hilos he visto cosas
seen Win michu and miare
he visto he visto a Win michu y a miare
sharing some threads against me from their
compartiendo unos hilo contra mí de sus
friends the allies that I have been like this I have
amigos los aliades que me he quedado así
said man what is talking about in this
he dicho tío queé está hablando en este
thread now if this everything you are
hilo ahora si esto todo lo que estás
saying in the thread is a lie but it is that
diciendo en el hilo es mentira pero es
I spend 5 years after
que paso yo ya 5 años después de de
answering something that is more than
contestarle a una cosa que está más que
there are the videos really it is that I
que ahí están los vídeos de verdad es
get lazy when I am not
que me da me dan pereza cuando no estoy
when
cuando
when it seems very good to me to debate
cuando a mí me parece muy bien debatir
with everyone who has to debate eh I mean
con todo el que tenga que debatir eh o
with everything I do not care eh Javi I have not
sea con todo me da igual eh Javi no he
been online lately what do you think
estado conectado últimamente qué piensas
about alali's only I do not know if you have already
sobre el only de alali no sé si ya
talked about the subject but I would like to know your
hablaste del tema pero quisiera saber tu
opinion now we will see it now we will see
opinión ahora lo vemos ahora lo vemos
that I do not care to answer whoever it
que a mí me da igual contestarle al que
is what they say about me whatever they want and
sea lo que digan de mí lo que quiera y
whoever wants to upload here tell me you
el que quiera que suba aquí me lo diga
understand but people who are not even
me entiendes pero gente que no está ni
in the spotlight people who are not being
en la palestra gente de la que no se
talked about and people who are not
está hablando y gente que no es
newsworthy come out to me with  One thing about the
noticiable que me salgan con una cosa de
2019 allies production list is that it gives me all the
2019 a mí es que eso me me da toda la
laziness in the world, I mean, not for nothing if it
pereza del mundo o sea yo no por nada si
becomes fashionable again and we have to
se pone de moda otra vez y hay que
talk but but these are things that I say it
hablar pero pero son cosas que yo digo
's that I don't care or rather, it's that
es que me es que me da igual o sea es
sincerely for what you want I don't care what you
que sinceramente por lo que tú quieras
tell me I don't know what you
me da igual lo que tú me digas no sé qué
want me to tell you, you know, these are
quieres que te diga sabes es que son
things that are, they are characters that
cosas que son son personajes que
resurface and take out that yes, aplo that yes I don't
reflotan y sacan que si aplo que si no
know what Like what am I going to tell you at this
sé qué Como qué te digo yo a estas
point, what am I going to tell you but anyway,
altura ya qué te digo pero bueno en fin
let's talk about the current topic
vamos a hablar de del del tema de la
that the current topic
actualidad que el tema de la actualidad
is much more interesting and deserves
es mucho más interesante y merece
much more attention no obviously
muchísimo más la pena no evidentemente
no what the [ __ ] are we going to talk about things here
no qué [__] vamos a hablar de cosas aquí
about nonsense from 2019 who are we Johan
de tonter de 2019 quién somos Johan
Plana let's talk about current things
plana vamos a hablar de cosas de la
interesting topics The ol
actualidad temas interesantes El ol fan
Ali fan well who says lolif Ali fan they
Ali bueno quien dice lolif fan del Ali
gave me these stickers the other day
me regalaron estas pegatinas el otro día
in a
en una
store they gave me these stickers I don't
tienda me regalaron estas pegatinas no
know where I'm going to stick them maybe I'll
sé dónde las voy a pegar a lo mejor me
get them as a tattoo
las hago de tatuaje
eh Who says  Ali's lifan says
eh Quién dice los lifan del Ali dice la
Ali's naughty roulette which is what
La ruleta traviesa del Ali que es lo que
has caught my attention the most in
a mí más me ha llamado la atención de
this whole story
toda esta historia
eh I mean careful eh careful eh careful
eh o sea cuidado eh cuidado eh cuidado
because suddenly everyone is
que de repente está todo el mundo como
freaking out with the photograph with the
flipando con la fotografía con la
leaked photograph of Ali but I'm like this I
fotografía filtradas del Ali pero yo me
say the photograph the
quedo así digo la fotografía las
photographs are the least of it what do I say
fotografías son lo de menos qué me decd
about The roulette The capricious roulette of Ali
de La ruleta La ruleta caprichosa de Ali
Wait wait I'll share it boom The
Espera espera que lo comparto pum La
capricious roulette of
ruleta caprichosa de
Ali eye eh
Ali ojo eh
eye
ojo
120 one spin
120 una tirada
200 two
200 dos
spins you save you save
tiradas te ahorras te ahorras
20 if you
20 si juegas dos chiladas
play two crap I mean it's a great deal it's a great deal What can you win in the Roulette What can you win The roulette Well look you can win cinema photo video sub free two days two days watching alali in her
días dos días viendo a alali en en sus
photos okay free
fotos vale gratis
eh special audio eye Lali sending you a
eh audio especial ojo Lali mandándote un
special audio because we haven't had
audio especial que no hemos tenido
enough with the audios that they've
suficiente con los audios que me han
sent me from all my friends about how he
mandado de todos los amigos de cómo
lied about how you had to lie Ricky
mentía de cómo había que mentir la Ricky
well special audio okay special audio
bueno audio especial vale audio especial
custom no  I know what sex
custom no sé lo que
sex dude So for
sex sex tío O sea que por
120 for
120 que por
120 you can do sexting with
120 puedes hacer sexting con
Lali audio sexing video hot video
Lali audio sexing video hot vídeo
special photos horny photos
especial fotos cachondas fotos cachondas
as if the rest of the photos were
como si el resto de fotos fueran
artistic you know it doesn't bother you but
artísticas sabes no te jode pero
listen to me listen to me listen to me
escúchame escúchame escúchame
sexting this sexting thing has killed me
sexting a mí lo de sexting me ha matado
eh I mean me that you're talking to me here
eh o sea yo que estáis hablándome
me that we're talking
aquí yo que estemos hablando aquí
nonsense here When we have a roulette wheel here let's
tonterías Cuando tenemos aquí una ruleta
see I was thinking the other day and
a ver yo estaba pensando el otro día y
people are criticizing me dude and it's like But
la gente criticándome tío y es como Pero
why me
por qué me
[Music]
[Música]
idiot idiot that could be any of
lelo lelo que podría ser cualquier ex
Ali's ex-boyfriend at the door of the
novio del Ali en la puerta de la
bookstore there was a huge store the
librería había una pedazo de tienda la
car my weakness okay But it's always
coche mi debilidad vale Pero siempre ha
been my weakness eh I mean not now
sido mi debilidad eh o sea no ahora
because things are going really bad for me
porque me vayan las cosas bien mal
because I'm a youtuber always eh I mean
porque sea youtuber siempre eh o sea
always if I had to if I had to go
siempre si me tenía que si me tenía que
without feeding my children to
quedar sin darle de comer a mis hijos
buy a JC the car was
por comprarme un JC la coche me
left to me I mean in the end what can I tell you what can I
quedaba O sea al final qué te digo qué
tell you I was now almost two
Te digo yo yo estaba ahora casi dos
months without eating to lose my belly  you
meses sin comer para perder la barriga
know Read it read it Read it read it Well
sabes Léelo léelo Léelo léelo Pues
always always I mean I can't
siempre siempre o sea yo no puedo
come across a store of that brand
cruzarme con una tienda de esa marca
because I love it I love clothes and I
porque me encanta me fascina la ropa y
was doing a live stream I did a live stream
estaba hice un directo hice un directo
to say hello to the
para para saludar a
gentlemen I
señoreros sé cuánto no Y entonces le
know how much no And then I was telling the ladies I have a store in front of me that is my weakness I went in I bought a sweater I bought a sweater damn I'm in another country 600 km from my house I mean damn it's a sweater that I'm not going to find anywhere else so I'll
voy a encontrado en otro lado pues me lo
buy it a gsei
compro un gsei
but to be honest to be honest
pero en honor a la verdad en honor a la
eh yeah if I could have
eh si si hubiera
I would have bought a couple
podido me hubiera comprado un par de
more things that I saw that seemed
cositas más que vi que me parecieron
too expensive and I didn't buy them
demasiado caras y no me las compré
one was a
una fue un
tracksuit because they wanted to charge me for one I
chandal porque me querían cobrar por un
mean it was worth the tracksuit [ __ ]
o sea es que valía el chandal [__]
the [ __ ] tracksuit was worth the same I
valía el [__] chanda lo mismo que me
[ __ ] on
cago en
10 I'm done I just came from Love by Ali
10 Ya terminé vengo de Love de Ali
rating that information wasn't necessary We didn't
rating no hacía falta ese dato No
want to know you wanted to know
queríamos saberlo ustedes queríais saber
that information  Someone who was here
ese dato alguien de los que estaban aquí
needed that information it's information
necesitaban ese dato es una información
that you can
que te puedes
save it's information that you can
ahorrar es una información que te puedes
save
ahorrar
says the garage the garage no no the
dice la cochería la la cochería no no la
garage I've always really liked
la cochería a mí siempre me ha gustado
the crocodile The thing is that
mucho el cocodrilo Lo que pasa que
lately nothing else comes close to the
últimamente nada más que se me acerca al
alligators but I like the crocodile I
lagartos pero a mí el cocodrilo Me gusta
really like the chanda
mucho el chanda
300 a chanda a chanda I'm not going to
300 un chanda un chanda no me lo voy a
wear it a chanda the cocho I'm not going to
poner un chanda la cocho no me lo I a
wear it for the
poner para el
gym chanda leave it but then there was a
gimnasio chanda dejalo pero luego hubo
jacket there was a
una chaqueta hubo una
jacket there was one of these
chaqueta hubo una chaqueta de estas así
college jackets that I like
como universitarias que a mí me gustan
college style I don't know what and I
estilo universitarias no sé qué y
say weakness for two weakness for two
digo debilidad por dos debilidad por dos
rock a kiss handsome weakness for two
roca un beso guapo debilidad por dos
because I love those types of jackets Since I
porque me encantan ese tipo de chaquetas
'm very much a jacket wearer I need a
Yo como soy muy chaquetero necesito
lot I don't have them of all kinds it
muchas no las tengo de todas clases es
's true the jacket is what
que es verdad es que la chaqueta es lo
I like to wear the most jackets and
que más me gusta vestir las chaquetas y
the sweatshirt winter clothes in general
la sudadera la ropa invierno en general
are what I like the most
es lo que más me gusta
400 round
400 redondo
400 I say that it seems to me I say let's go that it seems like
400 digo que me parece Digo vamos que
a lot it seems to me it seems
mucho es que me parece me parece
very expensive I say  It seems
carísimo digo me parece
very expensive to me but above all of course it seems
carísimo pero sobre todo claro me parece
expensive to me No because no no because it is no because she wasn't
caro No porque no no porque sea no
pretty because
porque no fuera guapa porque
obviously what it has is the quality you
evidentemente lo que tien que la calidad
see you know 400 and I say it seems like a lot for the
vist sabes 400 y digo me parece mucho la
jacket to spend it for me to buy it
chaqueta para gastármelo yo comprármelo
you and the unworthy people because I had
ustedes y la la gente indigna porque le
told you that and I put a
había dicho yo eso y Pongo aquí una
Bar here just like I put Ah The
Barrita igual que he puesto Ah La
Bar of the members I put a
Barrita de los miembros Pongo aquí una
Bar here for the jacket it's
Barrita para la chaqueta que hace
cold I'm going to buy a bad jacket
frío me V a comprar una chaqueta mala
from cousin Javi the jacket maker but no that
del prima Javi el chaquetero pero no que
's the truth the
es la verdad la gente
unworthy people Aida a kiss sweetheart how are you I
ind Aida un beso corazón qué tal está te
heard you in that little while Javi that a
escuché en ese ratito Javi que a una
lady had a tantrum but it's
señora le entró la rabieta pero que es
true what can I say it seems expensive to me to
verdad qué te digo me parece cara para
buy it you from here put I don't
comprármela yo usted de aquí ponéis yo
know m 10 euros each you stop
que sé m 10 euritos cada uno dejáis de
smoking joints for a week and
fumar porros durante una semana y me
buy me the [ __ ] jacket that's why I
compráis la [__] chaqueta que para eso
'm here with
estoy aquí con
you I mean I don't understand I don't
ustedes o sea que no lo entiendo No lo
really understand But then
entiendo de verdad Pero entonces yo aquí
what
para qué
am I here for Well look instead of buying the
estoy Pues mira en vez de comprarme la
jacket instead of buying the
chaqueta en vez de comprarme la
jacket I could have four
chaqueta Podría tener cuatro
throws four and I don't think many
tiradas cuatro y tampoco creo que mucha
people play this be very careful eh because
gente juega esto mucho cuidado eh porque
there were almost 13,000 people already on it on
había casi 13000 personas ya en el en el
Telegram where olifan was leaked from
Telegram donde se filtraba olifan del
Ali I know from pure journalistic work I
Ali lo sé por puro trabajo periodístico
know from pure journalistic work okay
lo sé por puro trabajo periodístico vale
with four throws it's
con cuatro tiradas me toca
definitely my turn do you think that let's see with four throws it's definitely my
fijo creéis que a ver con cuatro tiradas
turn of course now I was
me toca fijo claro ahora estaba yo
thinking now I was thinking
pensando ahora estaba yo pensando
will it be worth it will it be worth
merecerá la pena merecerá la pena
risking my marriage for
jugarme el matrimonio por
Lali will it be worth risking my
Lali merecerá la pena jugarme el
marriage and the family life that I lead
matrimonio y la vida familiar que llevo
Raquel a kiss for Lali and of course the
Raquel un beso por Lali y claro la
question is also offensive no who wouldn't
pregunta también ofende no quién no la
do it no who no who no who wouldn't
haría no quién no quién no quién no se
risk it Who wouldn't risk it with
la jugaría Quién no se la jugaría con
a Lali What's up What's up that gives you more
una Lali Qué hay Qué hay que te dé más
confidence than being with a Dali
confianza que estar con una Dali
nothing let's
nada a
see let's see it's a risky sport no the way
ver a ver es deporte de riesgo no las
things are it's not a bit of a risky sport it
cosas como son no es un poco deporte de
's not a bit let's see but with four
no es un poco a ver pero con cuatro
throws it's your turn eh with four throws it's your turn it's your turn it's your turn the good one
tiradas te toca eh con cuatro tiradas te
no here the
toca te toca te toca la buena no aquí la
good one what would it be the sexting
buena cuál sería el el sexting
no the sexting
no el sexting
no I think I'd buy the jacket
no yo creo que me compro la chaqueta
better
mejor
polari
polari
[Music]
[Música]
eh I think the jacket is better eh
eh yo creo que es mejor la chaqueta eh
family When is my birthday Oh It was in
familia Cuándo mi cumple Ay Ha sido en
August [ __ ] for kings for Kings for
agosto [__] para reyes par Reyes par
Kings for King in advance okay for
Reyes para rey por adelantado vale para
King in advance then I put the bar
rey por adelantado luego pongo la barra
then I put the bar the bar I was going to
luego pongo la barra la barra iba a
say the line the
decir la raya la
line the one who has put the line the one who has
raya el que le han puesto la raya al que
put the line like that or I can't
le han puesto la raya así u no lo puedo
say that they sue me I wasn't going to say that they
decir que me demandan no iba a decir que
put the it's that I saw
le han puesto la es que he visto por ahí
a video somewhere there of a very
un vídeo que hay de una persona muy
nervous person but of course I can't say it they can't
nerviosa pero claro no lo puedo decir no
sue you no matter how nervous you are
te pueden demandar no por muy nerviosa
in the video well listen to
que hac en el vídeo bueno escúchame
me listen to me listen to me
escúchame escúchame escúchame
listen to me the roulette thing is a
escúchame lo de la Ruleta es una
fantasy eh I mean the roulette thing is
fantasía eh o sea lo de la Ruleta es
magical eh the roulette thing is amazing
mágico eh lo de la Ruleta es una pasada
Let's mean that I find out that
Vamos o sea que yo me encuentre con que
Lali has a roulette wheel this is like this
Lali tiene una ruleta esto es como esto
is magic I mean this is I think that
es magia o sea es que esto yo creo que
Ali has surpassed
Ali ha superado
eh any of the
eh cualquiera de las
eh I don't know how to classify them no so that I do
eh No sé que cómo calificarlas no para
n't I don't want any more lawsuits It's that I do
que no me que no quiero más demandas Es
n't want them to  sue me I stick around
que no quiero que me demanden me pego me
all day dodging demands It's that
pego todo el día esquivando demandas Es
then you guys say no but it's that
que luego ustedes decir no pero es que
pum pan it's that you ask for too much You want a
pum pan es que pides mucho Quieres una
[ __ ] jacket and me but if I stick around all
[__] chaqueta y yo pero si me pego todo
day I stick around every day dodging
el día me pego todos los días esquivando
demands I just dodged three demands
demandas acabo de esquivar tres demandas
in one moment and you haven't even
en un momento y no os habéis dado ni
noticed Javi it ​​looks like the roulette of
cuenta Javi se parece a la ruleta del
you know yes it can look like the roulette
you know sí se puede parecer a La ruleta
of yow Only the prize It's different
del yow Solo que el premio Es diferente
things as they are no let's see the prize is
las cosas como son no a ver el premio es
a little different let's
un poco diferente a
see This is a screenshot from my phone I have to
ver Esto es una captura de mi móvil
recognize it okay at 10:4 at
tengo que reconocerlo vale a las 10:4 de
night from ah no from Oporto not from Vigo I
la noche de ah no de oporto no de Vigo
took this screenshot I was in Vigo So
esta captura la hice estaba en vigo Así
this is Spanish time I was in Vigo I was in
que esto es hora española estaba en vigo
Vigo last night
estaba en vigo anoche
eh Lali lalia Lali Lala o fan more 18 I
eh Lali lalia Lali Lala o fan más 18 me
love the only fan more 18 you know how
encanta lo de only fan más 18 sabes como
son of a [ __ ] son of a
hijo de [__] hijo de
[ __ ] of course olifan more 18 It would be good
[__] claro olifan más 18 Estaría bueno
no
no
e
e
2424 this yesterdays this yesterdays
2424 esto ayeres esto ayeres
members
miembros
of which 746 were online at the
de los cuales 746 estaban online en ese
time I took the screenshot eh Javi Today there
momento que hice la captura eh Javi Hoy
are
hay
17000 oh my god man oh my god
17000 madre mía
The hippies eh be a lot of you
mía madre mía Los hipi eh sea muchos
mess with her
meteros con ella
but a lot with her
pero much con ella
but what are
pero pero a qué
you playing at let's see I'm going to I'm going to enter eh Ah
jugáis a ver voy a voy a entrar eh Ah
well Okay oh my god I just entered a
bueno Vale madre mía Acabo de entrar un
batito with Jacki it's time wasn't it
de batito con Jacki ya toca no estuvo
great a debate with Jacki I don't know
buenísimo un debatio con Jacki no sé yo
if Jacki was very much in the
si Jacki estaría muy por la
labz
labz
Eh well they've closed it No the group they haven't
Eh pues la han cerrado No el grupo no la
closed the group
han cerrado grupo
eh they've closed the
eh la han cerrado el
group it
grupo me
tells me it's been closed for
sale me sale que que ha sido cerrado por
pornographic material or something like that no let's
material pornográfico o algo así no a
see I'm going to enter Wait I'm going to enter
ver voy a entrar Espera voy a entrar
again there what is
otra vez ahí lo que me
displayed to me Because It was
displayed Because It was
Used To sprit pornographic
Used To sprit pornographic
content So you can't
content O sea que que no se
there's another one with 5000 but you can't you can't You
puede hay otro con 5000 pero no se puede
see I wanted to describe you a
no se puede Ya ve os quería describir un
little I wanted to describe you a little the
poco os quería describir un poco el
content but you can't you don't have to
contenido pero no se puede no hay que
give it anything special a friend told me that there is
darle algo en especial un amigo me dijo
others but it is not possible I did not
otros pero no se puede
want to describe the material a little
no os quería describir un poco el
to see what she has put me on the
material a ver qué me ha puesto sobre el
subject here luare in the script luar eh How did you
tema aquí luare en el guion luar eh Cómo
make a script about lly a fan of Ali
has hecho un guion sobre lly fan de Ali
okay this is the announcement When when she
vale esto es el anuncio Cuando lo cuando
announces it
lo anuncia
not when Lali sees that a Ricky
no cuando Lali vea que que un Ricky ya
can no longer support her she will end up opening
no la puede mantener se acabará abriendo
an only fan mark my
un only fan acuérdense de mis
words
palabras
lol
lol
Wow
Wow
eh host What a good sasca on the part of
eh [__] Qué buen sasca por parte de
princessita this you look it's true
princesita este tú mira es cierto
some of you need to show your
algunas necesitáis enseñar las
chetas
chetas
at least I go ahead and open an
por lo menos yo voy de cara y me abro un
ol fan to earn money with my body
ol fan para ganar dinero con mi cuerpo
You said that your thing was empowerment
Tú decías que lo tuyo era empoderamiento
Haha geek has broken you rali has
Jaja friky te ha reventado rali te ha
broken you princess 7800 likes
reventado princesita 7800 likes
princess princess based eh
princesita princesita basada eh
princess based I mean this is the most
princesita basada o sea esto es lo más
based that I have seen of princess
basado que he visto de princesita
after it was believed that she learned
después de que se creyera que aprendía
Catalan by opening the windows in Andorra they
Catalán abriendo las ventanas en andorra
erased it they rape her But she wants to continue
lo borraron la violan Pero quiere seguir
meeting the abuser and opens an
quedando con el abusador y se abre un
olifan for  celebrate it I feel so
olifan para celebrarlo me siento tan
[ __ ] stupid for having
jodidamente imbécil por haberla
defended her because I considered that a
defendido porque consideraba que una
friend was not going to cheat on me [ __ ]
amiga no me iba a engañar jodida
[ __ ] [ __ ] this is a friend not
retrasada hostias esto es un amigo no
because of what
por lo que
Javi says they just posted a video of yours
dice Javi acaban de poner un vídeo tuyo
on Ali's Telegram Look, I would
en el Telegram de Ali Mira yo ese cameo
n't stand for that cameo tell me it's a
no lo soportaría dime que es una
joke tell me it's a [ __ ] joke tell me it's a
coña dime que es una [__] coña
[ __ ]
dime que es una [__]
joke I mean I can't stand that [ __ ]
coña O sea no puedo soportar ese camón
if that's true they posted a video of mine
si eso es verdad han puesto un vídeo mío
on Telegram
en el Telegram
This but since it's the
Este pero ya que es lo
next thing they post a video of mine on the
siguiente que pongan un vídeo mío en
car forum but what video of mine have they posted
coche pero qué vídeo mío han puesto
to watch but it's a Well that's why they
a ver pero es un Pues por eso han
closed the group for pornographic content
cerrado el grupo por contenido
of course they posted a
claro han puesto un
papodo Wow you've left feeling comfortable eh
papote Válgame te has quedado a gusto eh
Manu you've disappointed me a lot Lali
Manu me has decepcionado muchísimo Lali
really you yourself know the affection that I
de verdad tú misma sabes el cariño que
've had for you throughout our
te he tenido a lo largo de nuestra
friendship because you've been a very
amistad porque ha sido una persona muy
important person to me you've helped me with
importante para mí me has ayudado con
all my problems blah blah blah blah
todos mis problemas bla bla bla bla bla
blah you
bla
can come to me with that I don't know the truth
me podrás venir con que no sé la verdad
And probably I don't know it but the
Y probablemente no la sepa pero las
actions that you're taking in your life
acciones que estás tomando en tu vida le
give more reason to what is  Speak
dan más razón a lo que se habla
publicly and you will know
públicamente que a tu verdad tú sabrás
where your life is going Lali I don't
hasta dónde conduces tu vida Lali no te
wish the worst on you but I don't wish the best on you either. Just
deseo lo peor pero tampoco lo mejor solo
think, reconsider and remember everything
que pienses recapacites Y reconda todo
because absolutely everyone
porque esto absolutamente todos
makes mistakes in their lives but it's
cometemos errores en nuestras vidas pero
never too late to improve and not all that
nunca tarde para mejorar y no todo ese
nonsense I'm only telling you this for the Lolly
rollo Solo te lo digo por el Lolly
fan.
fan
Sorry about all this nonsense. I'm not just
perdón todo este rollo no solo te lo
telling you this for the only fan. The topic you were
digo por el only fan tema del que te
laughing at and criticizing when we mentioned
reías y criticaba cuando mencionábamos a
other women who worked on this
otras mujeres que trabajaban en esta
platform. I'm not going to read all that. Manu, you have
plataforma no voy a leer todo eso Manu
n't had the decency to talk
no has tenido la decencia de hablar
to me in all this time nor have you
conmigo en todo este tiempo ni te has
worried about the situation or my version.
preocupado por la situación o mi versión
But you're uploading the video to look good
Pero subes el tchaco para quedar bien
in front of people, like I've already told you,
delante de la gente como ya te he dicho
the word friend has become too
la palabra amigo se te ha quedado
big for you, okay Lali. I sent this to
grande vale Lali Esto se lo mandé a otra
someone else. Put it on, uncle Lali. What a
persona Pon tío Lali Qué
liar,
mentirosa
p if you need us to go to Zaragoza to
p si necesitas que vayamos a zaragosza a
be with you. Put it on
estar con Pon
Lali, you've just lost what little respect
Lali acabas de perder el poco respeto
I had left for
que me quedaba
you, six bucks for 31 days, you have
contigo seis pavitos por 31 días tienes
Ali, eh
al Ali eh
my goodness,
mía
6.25
6,25
bucks.
pavitos
Don't you see the cane people are giving him?
no ve la caña que le está dando la gente
Eh no  look at the cane that people are giving him
Eh no vea la caña que le está dando la
Eh well now we see what
Eh bueno ahora vemos lo que ha
Ricky has answered How is my
respondido Ricky Cómo está mi
Peña well six turkeys how many people
Peña bueno seis pavitos cuánta gente
will have
habrá
paid or rather how many people will there be look at
pagado o sea cuánta gente habrá fíjate
you eh because in
tú eh porque en
reality cameo of reven cameo of reven
realidad cameo de reven cameo de reven
over there a kiss reven and clone what buckets
por ahí un beso reven y clona vaya cazos
not that they know that this would not have happened
no que sepan que esto no hubiera pasado
If only someone had
Si tan solo alguien hubiese llevado
only kept this in private what about Lolly
únicamente esto en privado lo de Lolly
you say what about
dices lo de
Lolly m I
Lolly m
don't know I think it's something that goes into
No sé yo creo que es algo que que va en
her or rather by itself No but I think that
ella o sea de por sí No pero yo creo que
Ali has already been like Lali has been like
el Ali ha sido ya como Lali ha sido como
eh any of these characters of
eh cualquier personaje de estos
the girls like that not like Lali that
de de las chicas así no como Lali que
we have criticized liars and so on no well
hemos criticado mentirosas y demás no
she has taken the profile to the maximum
pues ella ha llevado el perfil al máximo
not in exaggeration not in lies in
no de exageración no en mentiras en
slander
calumnia
in inventing something about someone eh she
en inventarse algo de alguien eh ella lo
has taken it like to the [ __ ]
ha llevado como al como al putísimo
extreme no and suddenly two
extremo no y de repente a las dos
weeks later appears with a LoL
semanas aparec con un LoL
fan Javi has put it
fan Javi lo ha puesto
25 but how many people will have paid or rather
25 pero cuánta gente habrá pagado o sea
because look at you eh Imagine you believe
porque fíjate tú eh Imagínate te creas
in  LoL fan you take those photos that are
en LoL fan te haces esas fotos que
also ordinary and
encima son ordinarias y son fotos
pornographic photos But also bad eh They are
pornográficas Pero además mal eh Son
pornographic photos But also super
fotos pornográfica Pero además super
ordinary super you know
ordinaria super sabes
and And
y Y
on top of that one thing that are photographs
encima una cosa que ya son fotografías
that everyone is going to have for
que todo el mundo va a tener ya para
life, I mean tomorrow
toda la vida o sea el día de mañana
any cousin any
cualquier primo cualquier
eh Javi what do we have to do for a
eh Javi qué tenemos que hacer para una
roulette of yours face with hand over mouth
ruleta tuya cara con mano sobre la boca
arcalia buy me that jacket from the
arcalia comprarme la chaqueta esa de la
car that I want to buy the
coche que la quiero comprarme la
jacket or rather how many people are here
chaqueta o sea cuánta gente hay aquí
1600 people How much do 1600
1600 personas A cuánto caben 1600
people fit I think they fit at 2 euros each
personas creo que caben a 2 eur cada uno
more or less Well at 2 euros at 2 euros no at
más o menos Bueno a 2 eur a 2 eur no a
50 cents no How much would they fit at 50 at
50 céntimos no A cuánto cabrían a 50 a
25 cents each cabri I
25 céntimos cada uno cabri
didn't see it there I can't give an opinion well they are
ahí no la vi no puedo opinar bueno son
photographs that everyone is going to have
fotografías que todo el mundo va a tener
always I mean in the end they are photographs of
siempre o sea al final son fotografías
you that everyone is going to have your
tuyas que todo mundo va a tener tu
family you what do I know I mean it's a
familia tu yo que sé o sea es que es
lot of fabric at what point does it occur to you
mucha tela en qué momento se le ocurre
that after lying about something so serious it
que después de mentir con algo tan grave
is the best idea to go back with  an only
es la mejor idea volver con un only
fan let's see what Ricky has responded
fan vamos a ver lo que ha respondido
edit well Ricky Edi has uploaded a photo
edit bueno Ricky Edi ha subido una foto
playing with his cat first of all with
jugando con su gato eso lo primero con
Ali's cat not the cat that
el gato de Ali no con el gato por el que
Ali is going to
Ali va a
fight for they just
batallar me acaban de
finished me
me acaba
Elisa Elisa just sent me a visa
Elisa Elisa me acaba de mandar un visum
and it says 2 euros I don't know how to become a member
y me pone 2 eur no sé hacerme miembro un
kiss
beso
Elisa but it's
Elisa pero es
that she usually sends me visas from time to time
que me suele mandar de vez en cuando
now that I see it and she always writes me the
visum ahora que lo veo y me escribe
same thing I don't know how to become a member I don't
siempre lo mismo No sé hacerme miembro
know how to become a member well okay It's okay it's okay let's
no sé hacerme miembro bueno vale No pasa
see I think that the
nada no pasa nada a ver yo creo que la
jacket would at least be a good
chaqueta mínimo sería un buen reg de
welcome gift eh I mean what happens is that it's
bienvenida eh o sea lo que pasa que me
a bit far away for me now how
pille ya un poco lejos ya por ella cómo
could we do it let's see think a little
lo podríamos hacer a ver pensar un poco
Well this is going to be the next
Bueno este va a ser el próximo
cat I was going to name the cat but
gato iba a ponerle nombre al gato pero
I'm going to dodge the demands Okay I'm going to
voy a esquivar las demandas Vale Voy a
dodge the demands But well this is going to
esquivar las demandas Pero bueno este va
be the next cat that
a ser el próximo gato por el que van a
not a couple of youtubers are going to fight for now
batallar no un par de youtubers ahora
Well let's read Ricky's response
Bueno vamos a leer el la respuesta de
let's read Ricky's response
Ricky vamos a leer la respuesta de Ricky
Ramón Oy man Beatriz is gorgeous there
Ramón Oy hombre Beatriz guapísima hay
signs of something sicker don't measure the
señales de algo más enfermo no mide el
damage that's being done I think it's
daño que se está haciendo creo que
starting to stop being funny the bad thing is
empieza a dejar de ser gracioso lo malo
what she and Ricky did to
es lo que ella y Ricky les hicieron a
the
los
kids the bad thing is what she and Ricky
chavales lo malo es lo que ella y Ricky
did to the kids to the
le hicieron a los chavales a los
kids you mean those who
chavales te refieres a los que acusaron
falsely accused no I blocked her a long time ago from
en falso no la bloqueé hace tiempo de
everywhere because I didn't want to know anything
todas partes porque no quería saber nada
more about her I almost always end up
más de ella casi siempre me terminan
getting the things she posts and I'm
llegando las cosas que sube y estoy
tired of silencing everyone who
cansado de silenciar a todo el que me
sends them to me Look Ricky eh you're
las manda Mira Ricky eh tú estás
commenting on this because you feel like it I mean
opinando de esto porque te da la gana o
literally you're commenting on this
sea literalmente estás opinando esto
because you want Lali is trending and it could
porque quieres Lali es tendencia y podrá
be trending it could be trends
ser en tendencia podrá ser tendencias a
from now on as many times as I
partir de ahora todas las veces que
want there you have it for the jacket
quiera ahí tienes para la chaqueta
398 very good very good good math
398 muy bien muy bien buenas matemáticas
also smer iser very good very good that's how
además smer iser muy bien muy bien así
I like it That's how I
me gusta Así me
like it Ángel crepus a kiss welcome That's how I like it
gusta Ángel crepus un beso bienvenido
kids That's how I like it
Así me gusta chavales Así me gusta
man I'm making an effort here
hombre estoy haciendo aquí un esfuerzo
not to read these tw no and everything
no de leer estos tw no y todo
no it wasn't AB egg to comment it wasn't
no no era AB huevo opinar no era de
egg to comment he's commenting because he
huevo opinar está opinando porque él
wants to comment he's  giving your opinion because you
quiere opinar está opinando porque
want us to read this I mean imagine
quiere que leamos esto O sea imagínate
now Lali that
ahora Lali que de
suddenly in a week it's
repente dentro de una semana es
trending because she's hooking up
tendencia porque se enrolla
with
con
Loeda it'll be trending again you don't
loeda será tendencia otra vez tú no
have to give your opinion It's not that I've seen
tienes por qué opinar No es que me ha
that it's reached you it's not that it's a
llegado a ver que te ha llegado no es
trend people tag you or they
que es tendencia la gente te etiqueta o
don't tag you But what does it matter
no te etiqueta Pero qué más da
sharom Thank you thank you thank you everyone
sharom Gracias gracias gracias a todos
thank you
gracias a
everyone this because she wanted to give her opinion okay It's not
todos esto porque ha querido opinar vale
that it reached her or that it didn't reach her
No es que le haya llegado ni que no le
you can't avoid that you
haya llegado eso no lo puedes evitar tú
can't avoid
ya no puedes evitar
that anymore Thanks for the visa Elisa Ah a
eso Gracias por el visum Elisa Ah un
kiss Elisa you're here sweetheart Thank you very much
beso Elisa estás por aquí corazón Muchas
darling macho Thank you very much
gracias cariño macho Muchas gracias
queen letting her do whatever the hell she wants
reina dejarla hacer lo que le dé la gana
a dose of reality that reveals her as a
un golpe de realidad que la revela como
false victim of rape unfaithful partner
falsa víctima de violación pareja infiel
and compulsive liar forces you
y mentirosa compulsiva te obliga o bien
to either disappear from the internet and come back
a desaparecer de internet y volver
in a while when everything has
dentro de un tiempo cuando todo haya
passed to apologize or take advantage
pasado para disculparte o aprovecharte
of the situation no matter what
de la situación dando igual lo
happened
sucedido
[Music]
[Música]
Ricky
Ricky
you You also accompanied her and
tú Tú también la acompañaste y la
helped her lie in what you knew she
ayudaste a mentir en lo que tú sabías
was
que estaba
lying but it's not
mintiendo pero es que todavía no
just that Ricky forgets  that
solamente es que Ricky se le olvida que
he messed with the people who didn't believe
él se metió con la gente que no creía a
Ali he even messed with me okay
Ali se metió incluso conmigo vale
disappointed you could have trusted me
decepcionado podrías haberme fíate tu
Ricky mobin a
Ricky mobin un
kiss remember the tweet that Ricky sent me
beso acordaros del tweet que me puso
that I can't see it now because he
Ricky que no lo puedo ver ahora porque
has blocked me
me tiene bloqueado
393 a kiss tesa gorgeous Thank you so much
393 un beso tesa guapísima Muchísimas
the whole chat congratulate tesa it
gracias todo el chat felicitar a tesa
's her birthday today she turns 25
que es su cumpleaños hoy cumple 25
oh my goodness we want to see the jacket look for
añazos madre mía la chaqueta queremos
it on the page but
verla Búscala en la página pero es que
the Chan
la chaqueta Chan
oporto jacket I don't know if I'm going to
oporto yo no sé si me si me la Vais a
buy it I don't know how I'm going to go for it
comprar no sé cómo voy a ir por ella
but oh well first buy it and then we'll
pero bueno primero comprármela y luego
see hepi a kiss m that Ricky when I
ya vem hepi un beso m que Ricky cuando
released that video that I didn't
yo saqué el vídeo ese de que no me la
believe her that she was a false
creía de que era una falsa víctima de
rape victim that all these exclusives that I
violación de que todas las exclusivas
released because all these
estas que saqué porque todas las
exclusives that I
exclusivas estas que
released the only thing that was not
saqué lo único que lo único que no era
true was what I already said that it
verdad era lo que yo ya dije que no
was not proven that it was true that it was
estaba comprobado que era verdad que era
that conversation that came out that maybe he
la conversación esa que salió que igual
said it himself in the video he himself
el mismo lo dijo en el el vídeo él mismo
said it in the video that conversation
lo dijo en el vídeo que esa conversación
that I released in that
que yo saqué en ese
video was almost the same as a
vídeo era casi Igual que una
conversation that was real, I mean there were
conversación que era real o sea existían
conversations almost the same as that one that
conversaciones casi iguales que esa que
were leaked and I saw them and I saw them and I
se filtraron y yo las vi y yo las vi y
can have them and I can put them what
las puedo tener y las puedo poner lo que
happens is that I'm not going to
pasa es que no las voy a
put them Look for it on the cars page
poner Búscala en la página de la coches
and show it to us to see contribution for
y nos la enseña a ver contribución para
the expensive jacket throwing a Thank you
la chaqueta cara lanzando un Gracias
Rocío Look at the kids if they buy it for me man let's see the
Rocío Mira la chavalería si me la compra
kids if they buy it for me
tío a ver la chavalería si me la compra
then the lordship was
luego la señoría me estaba
criticizing me let's see I don't know what it's
criticando a ver es que no sé cómo se
called
llama
Javi here I contribute my
esoy Javi aquí aporto mis
200 a
200 un
kiss I don't know what it's
beso es que no sé cómo se
called Let's
llama
see look this is the [ __ ]
A ver Mira este es el [__]
tracksuit This is the [ __ ] tracksuit Look at the
chandal Este es el [__] chandal Mira la
top mother of God it's really abusive
arriba madre de Dios es que abusa mucho
but it's very pretty Let's see wait it's
pero es que es muy bonito A ver espérate
surely
que seguro que está
here it's here for sure
aquí está aquí seguro
man I'm sorry eh I'm starting to
tío lo lo siento eh lo empiezo a
notice
notar
no let's see there's one here that's not the
no a ver está una aquí que no es la
same
misma
Exactly it's not the same
Exactamente no es la misma
exactly 800 You think it's worth
exactamente 800 Tú te crees que vale
but 800 mother of God
pero 800 madre de Dios
391 Congratulations weighs buy the
391 Felicidades pesa compra la chaqueta
800 euro jacket another one let's see but besides that one I don't
800 eur otra a ver pero aparte esa no me
like it eh Not that one for 800 no eh the
gusta eh Esa no la de 800 no eh la de
800 I don't
800 No me
like it in case I was thinking of going to buy it for
gusta por si pensaba ir comprármela de
800 no eh I don't see it
800 no eh No la veo
Oh I don't
Oh no la
see it I don't
veo
see it I'm missing two
veo me faltan dos
[Music]
[Música]
pages I don't see it it's not there it's not there What a shame What a
páginas no la veo no
shame eh that I lost the
Qué pena eh que he perdido la
opportunity eh it's that the
oportunidad
whole
eh es que está toda
the whole new collection is there but it's not there that one is not there That's
la está toda la colección nueva pero no
strange man but they sneak in
raro tío pero se cuelan
eh they sneak in
eh se cuelan
a lot
mucho
Wait I'll find it in a
Espera que la encuentro en un
second it's not there It's probably sold out
segundo no está No está se habrá agotado
Oh it's probably
Oh se habrá
sold out it's sold out
agotado se ha agotado
guys oh it's
chavales
sold out for the 800 come on I'm not going to
vaya se ha agotado por la de 800 venga
be rude to her either we're not going to be rude to the 800 We
tampoco no le vamos a serer feo a la 800
all want to see the expensive jacket
Todos queremos ver la chaqueta cara
smiling with her eyes closed gu but
sonriendo con los ojos cerrados gu pero
anyway like anyway No maybe there
de todas manera como de todas manera No
wasn't even a miall Because the one that
a lo mejor no había ni miall Porque la
was outside was the
estaba afuera era la
s
s
Okay guys let her do whatever she wants
Bueno chicos dejadla hacer lo que le dé
a dose of reality that
la gana un golpe de realidad que la
reveals her as a false victim  of rape
revela como falsa víctima de violación
unfaithful partner and compulsive liar they
pareja infiel y mentirosa compulsiva te
force you to disappear from the internet and
obligan bien a desaparecer de internet y
come back in a while when everything
volver dentro de un tiempo cuando todo
has passed to apologize or take
haya pasado para disculparte o
advantage of the situation regardless of
aprovecharte de la situación dando igual
what happened
lo sucedido
him when I broke the exclusives that I
él cuando yo saqué las exclusivas que yo
broke in the conversations in the
en las conversaciones saqué en las
exclusives I even broke one day the
exclusivas saqué Incluso un día la
conversation of Ella telling her
conversación de Ella diciéndole a las
friends you have to lie like
amigas tenéis que mentir como en
scoundrels that I broke one day too
bellacas eso lo saqué yo un día también
Well when he blocked me he said I did
Bueno pues él cuando me bloqueó me dijo
n't expect that from you you have
no me lo esperaba de ti me has
disappointed me I don't know what I don't know how much
decepcionado no sé qué no sé cuánto
and you could have consulted me he said you
y podrías haberme consultado dijo
could have consulted me because you
podrías haberme consultado porque tú
had access to us to have
tenías acceso a nosotros para habernos
asked us look at you I would have asked him
preguntado fíjate tú que le llego a
look at you I would have
preguntar fíjate tú que le llego a
asked him
preguntar
eh that I would have asked them eh In order for them to
eh que les lleo a preguntar eh Para que
confirm something they were
me confirmen ellos dos algo estaban
both lying my testimony was neither revenge
dos mi testimonio no fue ni una venganza
nor an attack on me it was a
ni un ataque a mala fue una disculpa
sincere apology for having allowed her to use
sincera por haberla permitido utilizar
my channel to cover up a false
mi canal para encubrir un falso abuso
sexual abuse Thank you for so many hours of
sexual Gracias por tantas horas de
entertainment and for keeping us up to date
entretenimiento y por tenernos al día
both the kids and the
tanto a la chavalería como a la
gentlemen only salty kiss Congratulations
señoreros único salador bes Felicidades
a kiss Thank you very much eh and blame the
un beso Muchas gracias eh e inculpar a
innocent who you covered as guilty from
inocente que techó como culpable desde
the beginning but yes Ricky but
el principio pero que sí Ricky pero que
now he is admitting that he cheated on you
ahora está reconociendo que te puso los
and that she was not a raped girl
cuerno y que no era una chica violada
but that you still have not
pero que todavía no habéis
recognized that you could still do it
reconocido que todavía podríais hacerlo
because it is October 16th
porque estamos a 16 de
Lali has a month to withdraw the
Lali tiene un mes para retirar la
complaint Lali has a month to withdraw
denuncia Lali tiene un mes para retirar
the complaint Alex that I think she
la denuncia Alex que yo creo que es lo
can
puede
withdraw it I think that if it does not go to trial
retirar Yo creo que si no llega a juicio
maybe I am wrong eh Maybe I am
a lo mejor me equivoco eh A lo mejor me
wrong and it is no longer possible eh but I
equivoco y ya no se puede eh pero yo
think that if it has not gone to trial and
creo que si no ha llegado a juicio y
she wants to cancel it I think it is
ella lo quiere cancelar creo que se
possible because with the ex she is not
puede porque con el ex tampoco está
telling the truth either, I mean it is her is her
diciendo la verdad o sea es su es su
pattern it is her modus
patrón es su modus
operandi but if he also blamed the
operandi pero si él también lo culpó al
kid but if it is that eh the two
pibe pero si es que eh los los dos
blame the ex-boyfriend or rather Ricky Ricky edy
culpan al exnovio o sea Ricky Ricky edy
said that the trial that Lali had had
dijo que el juicio que tenía Lali tenía
some evidence well she had some
unas pruebas bueno tenía unas pruebas
incredible evidence to blame the other for
increíbles para culparlo al otro de
abuse she said that in the video that is
maltrato eso lo dijo en el vídeo que
deleted and  in the others also in
tiene borrado y en los otros también en
the video that he uploads to Twitter and I don't know what
el vídeo que sube a Twitter y no sé qué
when are you going to portray that that is
cuándo os vais a retratar de eso que eso
also a
también es
lie that is
mentira
also a lie when are you going to
eso también es mentira cuándo os vais a
portray that come on you have already portrayed yourselves you
retratar de eso venga ya os habéis
have already portrayed yourselves about
retratado ya os habéis retratado de de
the rape when are you going to
lo de de la violación cuándo os vais a
portray yourselves also about the Tudor that
retratar también de lo del tudor que eso
is also a
también es
lie you know why that does not matter to you
mentira sabes por qué eso te da igual
Ricky because that does not affect you
Ricky porque eso no te afecta a ti a ti
this you this you are not apologizing for
esto tú esto no te estás disculpando por
the boy you are apologizing for your
el chaval tú te estás disculpando por tu
ego the whole time it has moved your
ego a ti todo el tiempo te ha movido el
ego the whole time it has moved your ego I
ego Todo el tiempo te ha movido el ego o
mean first of all you
sea en primer en primer
couldn't assume that you the famous one
lugar no podías asumir que tú el famoso
in the relationship the famous and the rich one in the
de la relación el famoso y el rico de la
relationship was the one being cheated on
relación era al que le ponían los
you couldn't
cuernos tú eso no lo podías
assume that me A chick cheats on me
asumir a mí me Pon los cuernos una pava
for a bucho bye I am a chick that I have been
por bucho chao que yo s una pava que
with for a year and out of the year out of
llevo un año con ella y del año de los
12 months I have seen four Maybe
12 meses me he visto cuatro A lo mejor
if I add up all the days  don't step foot here anymore
si sumo todos los días no pisa más aquí
Andorra is going to come for the cat the cat I'll
andorra va a venir por el gato el gato
send it to you for sure [ __ ] it's going to come for
te lo mando por segú [__] va a venir por
the
el
cat the cat I'll eat it [ __ ]
gato el gato me lo como [__] vas a venir
you're going to come for the cat me Tell me a story a girl it
tú por el gato me Pon un cuen una tía te
might hurt you and you might feel such okay It hurts you're
puede doler y te puede sentir tal vale
crazy okay whatever
Te duele estás en [__] illo vale lo
you want but you add up the days
que tú quieras pero tú sumas los días
that you've been with her in the year that you've been
que tú has estado con ella en el año que
you how long you've been with her
has estado tú cuánto has estado con ella
but oh well whatever you want the
pero bueno lo que tú quieras la La
thing is that he
Movida es que él
went along with his wife's lie
le siguió el rollo a la parienta de
for ego for ego it's all for
mentir por el ego por el ego todo es por
ego I mean if you notice if you
ego O sea si te das cuenta si te das
notice the first thing he does is force her
cuenta lo primero que hace es obligarla
force her to post a
ella obligarla a ella a que ponga un
tweet Why the [ __ ] do you have to make it
tweet Por qué [__] tenéis que llevarlo a
public Why Why do you have to why do you have to make it
público Por qué Por qué hay que por qué
public if it's an
hay que llevarlo a lo público si es una
intimate thing it doesn't have to be because nobody knows nobody finds
cosa íntima no lo tiene por qué sabe
out nobody finds out
nadie nadie se entera nadie se entera de
anything I mean who's going to find out nobody finds out
nada o sea quién se va a enterar nadie
Why nobody finds out and
se entera Por qué nadie se entera y
even Nothing happens Why the [ __ ] does the
hasta No pasa nada Por qué [__] se tiene
internet have to find out what he
que enterar internet de lo que te ha
did to you because you want it and your ego
hecho pues porque tú quieres y tu ego
wants her to get
quiere que ella reciba un
punished that she gets a I mean you he
castigo que ella reciba un O sea tú él
wanted like to get back with her not to
quería como volver con ella no volver
forgive her but of course his ego as a man does
perdonarla pero claro su ego de hombre
n't let him he wanted her to
no le deja él quería que ella
publicly acknowledge and
reconociera públicamente se fustigar
publicly flog the girl
públicamente la chica
and for people to tell him Oh well you
y y que la gente le dijera Ah pues te
've behaved badly with Ricky our Ricky
has portado mal con Ricky nuestro Ricky
is the best that's the first
es el mejor esa es el primer movimiento
ego move Come on again the cat good JJ
de ego Hala otra vez el gato bueno JJ
well what do you want me to tell you I'm
pues qué quieres que te diga tengo
hungry I'll eat the cat I'll eat it I'll eat it
hambre me lo como al gato me lo
and I'll make the jacket
como me lo como y me hago la chaqueta
that you didn't buy me with the cat
que no me habéis comprado con el gato
listen to me
escúchame
[Music]
[Música]
and I don't even know why the [ __ ] you watch
e Yo es que no sé ni por qué [__] veis
this channel La Movida is that the
este canal la La Movida es eso lo
first the second ego move
primero el segundo movimiento de ego
was to go along with the idea that she had been
fue seguirle el rollo de que la habían
raped so he wouldn't acknowledge that it was a
violado para él no reconocer que era un
con
con
nuto and to contradict
nudo y para llevarle la contraria al
Dallas and he spent a [ __ ] week
Dallas y se puso durante una [__] semana
making a video for Dallas dude I mean you have
hacerle vídeo al Dallas tío O sea tienes
a personal sentimental problem that
un problema personal sentimental que te
affects you and everything and you go with Dallas
afecta y todo y te pones con el Dallas
dude and you go with
tío y te pones con el
Dallas what the [ __ ] does it matter what a
Dallas qué [__] importa lo que diga un
youtuber says about your
youtuber de tu
relationship what the [ __ ] does it matter  what a
relación qué [__] importa lo que diga un
youtuber says about your relationship and more a guy that
youtuber de tu relación y más un tío que
you say shouldn't be taken seriously
tú dices que no hay que tomarlo en serio
than what Dallas says It doesn't matter that I don't
que lo que diga Dallas No importa que no
know what if he made videos all over the
sé qué si hizo vídeos todo
internet all over the internet or the subject of
internet todo internet o sea el tema de
Ricky Eddie's horns I think it has
los cuernos de Ricky Eddie yo creo que
been one of the few topics that I have seen
ha sido de los pocos temas que he visto
that everyone comments on Now when
que todo el mundo comenta Ahora cuando
Lali has opened up the hly fan I have seen
Lali se ha abierto los hly fan he visto
all the big youtubers challenging
a todos los youtubers grandes retando
giving likes and things about Ali it is a
dando likes y cosas sobre el Ali es un
subject that everyone has given their opinion on and
tema del que ha opinado todo el mundo y
Ricky Eddie the opinion that mattered to him
a Ricky Eddie la opinión que le importó
was
fue la de
Dallas's a guy that he doesn't
Dallas un tío con el que no se
talk to I mean what what what the [ __ ] is he
habla O sea qué qué qué [__]
doing Why haven't you made a series for
hace Por qué no le has hecho una serie a
each of those who have given their opinion or have
cada uno de los que han opinado o han
said something about the subject because of what
dicho algo sobre el tema por lo que diga
Dallas says whatever Dallas says a
Dallas lo que diga Dallas una
series a
serie una
series and there were a lot of people based based
serie y había un montón de gente basado
based the response Dallas oh oh he
basado basado la respuesta Dallas oh oh
put a clip of Dallas laughing at
ha puesto un cli de Dallas riéndose de
someone because he's fat Wow stupid
alguien porque está gordo Wow vasado
Ricky what the [ __ ] does that matter with what you
Ricky qué [__] importa eso con lo que
're
estáis
doing dala a series he brought his wife
haciendo dala una serie se trajo a la
running from Zaragoza to
parienta corriendo de zaragosza para
Andorra made a teaser, he recorded the series
andorra hizo un teaser grabó la serie
twice, once with his girlfriend and once without,
dos veces una con la novia y otra sin la
and the guy was watching each
novia y el tío se iba viendo cada
episode more and more
capítulo más más
exhausted, and now that there's no
reventado y ahora cuando ya no hay por
way to hold on to it, because he knows that
dónde cogerlo porque sabe que no paran
things keep coming out that it was a lie, that he
de salir cosas de que era mentira que é
knew from day one. I mean,
lo sabía desde el primer día O sea
they established that he knew from
fijaron que él lo sabía desde el primer
day one with more information than us, that
día con más información que nosotros que
the guy had heard audios of his
el tío había escuchado audios de la
girlfriend sleeping with the
novia con acostándose con los
guys and the guy had the balls to record
tíos y el tío tuvo los huevos de grabar
the
el
video and the series, man. No, it's
el vídeo y la serie tío No si que es
true that all the information, there was a lot of
verdad que todos los datos hubo muchos
information that he had later, but there was
datos que los tuvo después pero hubo
some information that he had from the
algunos datos que los tenía desde el
first moment and we did
primer momento y nosotros
n't know that it was a lie,
no sabiendo que era mentira
man. Of course, that's how you didn't want to debate with
tío Claro así no querías debatir con el
Dallas. That's how you didn't want to debate with Dallas. Of
Dallas así no quería debatir con el
course, how are you going to want to if you're
Dallas claro cómo vas a querer si estás
lying and you know it yourself? When you
mintiendo y tú mismo lo sabes cuando tú
're sure that you're right, you
estás seguro de que tienes razón tú
debate with whoever it
debates con el que
is. I just read a comment that I'm not
sea Acabo de leer un comentario que no
going to read out loud because you're
lo voy a leer en voz alta porque sois
sons of
unos hijos de
[ __ ], and the guy is now making the video to
[__] y el tío ahora hace el vídeo para
wash his
lavarse en las
hands so as not to look bad. He wants to look
manos para no quedar mal Él para quedar
like  that he has acknowledged the mistake and
como que él ha reconocido el error y se
has apologized no man but you have
ha disculpado no tío pero me habis
lied to me in everything but if it is that here he
mentido en todo pero si es que aquí
still does not recognize all the
todavía no está reconociendo todas las
lies still here he does not
mentiras todavía aquí no está
recognize all the lies man what did
reconociendo todas las mentiras tío que
you start saying that the that the
te pusiste a decir que la que que el
police when you told him
policía cuando le dijiste el nombre del
Dallas's name told you the history that Dallas had
Dallas te dijo el historial que tenía el
man Javi do you think that Lali will report Ricky
tío Javi crees que Lali denunciará Ricky
Of course I have no doubt
Por supuesto no me cabe ninguna duda
keep this
guardar este
and it's not that I want it I wish she doesn't
y no es que se lo desee Le deseo que no
do it but I have no doubt it is
lo haga pero no me cabe ninguna duda es
the profile Lali is the But look let's
el perfil Lali es el Pero mira vamos a
see think about one thing of all the
ver pensa en una cosa de todas las
stories like this of girls who lie and
historias así de chicas que mienten y se
make up things and all that stuff that
inventan cosas y todo el rollo ese que
we have talked about on this channel
hemos comentado en este canal
and Lali has been like the most
e Lali ha sido como el el perfil más
super
super
exaggerated profile I mean she has taken it to
exagerado O sea ella lo ha llevado a
another level lying accusing How can she not
otro nivel el mentir el acusar Cómo no
report if that is part of the
va denunciar si eso es parte del
ingredient that these people have how is she not going
ingrediente que tienen esta gente cómo
to report Of course she is going to
no va a denunciar Claro que va a
report it the moment things start to
denunciarlo en el momento que se vaya
heat up heating up the
caldeando el ambiente caldeando el
atmosphere when she is already really angry
ambiente cuando ya se enfade muchísimo
with one of the  the Bibles that
ella con uno de los de las Biblias estas
Ricky writes she's going to grab him she's going to
que escribe Ricky ella va a cogerle va a
file a
poner una
complaint but that's it that's it let's go that's
denuncia pero eso está eso está vamos
not
eso ni
listed it's not
cotiza se ni
listed but you know what Ricky save
cotiza pero sab qu que Ricky guardar
this clip if he doesn't do it because he sees me
este clip si no lo hace porque me ve
because sometimes I know that he sees
porque algunas veces yo sé que él ve las
things when we talk about
cosas que cuando hablamos de
him and if you don't do it because he's seen
él y si no lo haces porque lo ha visto
the excerpt okay but When Tudor wins
el extracto vale pero Cuando tudor gane
the trial next month Ricky Edie will
el juicio del mes que viene Ricky edie
surely come out and say that he is
seguramente saldrá a decir que se ha
disappointed because
decepcionado porque también le ha
Lali also lied to him in fact that Eno created it and she
mentido Lali en hecho que eno la creó y
also lied about this it's like no no
también ha mentido en esto es como no no
no riy I'm telling you Jav Oliveira I
no riy estoy diciendo Yo jav oliveira te
'm telling you in an interview with
estoy diciendo yo en una entrevista con
the guy and I'm
el chico y te estoy
putting you I'm putting you but I know that
poniendo te estoy poniendo pero sé que
what
lo de
Tudor does is that what Tudor does is there there's this
tudor sí es que lo de tudor hay hay esto
dude if it is that simply with this
tío si es que ya simplemente con esta
capture it's no longer useful or in other words this thing about
captura ya ya ya no sirve o sea esto de
Tudor is Tudor sharing in his
tudor es tudor compartiendo en sus
stories
historias
eh a story of Ali when he is
eh una historia del Ali cuando está
reporting that supposed beating okay in
denunciando esa supuesta paliza vale en
which Ali He is also saying if you
la que el Ali Además está diciendo si
know something if you find it let
sabéis algo si lo encontráis avisarme a
me know or Tuor or it's that already  simply with
mí o a tuor oes que ya simplemente con
this the complaint is a lie
esto la denuncia es mentira
simply with this the complaint is a
simplemente con esto ya la denuncia es
lie
mentira
Ricky and these are things that I have
Ricky y esto son cosas que yo he
verified but apart from this apart from
comprobado pero aparte de esto aparte de
this as I tell in the video
esto como bien cuento en el vídeo
conversations and a lot of things
conversaciones y un montón de cosas
conversations and a lot of
conversaciones y un montón de
things I mean Ricky knows very well that the
cosas o sea Ricky sabe de sobr ima que
Ali thing is a lie that the Ali thing with
lo del Ali es mentira que lo de Ali
Conor is also a
conor también es
lie I have already been able to know what she is
mentira yo ya podido có es ella de
really like how much she cheated on me and how little she
verdad lo mucho que me engañó y lo poco
loved me and once I was aware of that I
que me quiso y una vez fui consciente de
stopped caring what she did
ello dejó de importarme lo que hisiera
what things she uploaded or who she was with It's that
qué cosas subiera o con quién
this is that this is
estuviera Es que esto es que esto
also a
también es
lie It's that this is also a lie
mentira Es que esto también es mentira
because you yourself recognize in the video
porque tú mismo reconoces en el vídeo
that when you see the video of Lali making out
que cuando ves el vídeo de Lali dándose
with her friend that you start to
el pico con el amigo que te pones a
tell her what she does
decirle que qué
And you tell that
hace Y eso lo cuentas tú eso lo cuentas
you tell that anyway right now I expect
tú en fin ahora mismo me espero
anything that would not surprise me However
cualquier cosa que no me sorprendería
little sense it makes for her to
Por poco sentido que tenga que me
report me that I make videos but I'm not
denuncie que haga vídeos pero no me
worried I'm ready to respond to
preocupa estoy listo para responder
any nonsense if necessary Ricky
cualquier tontería si es necesario Ricky
if she reports you it's not nonsense I'm not
si te denuncia no es una tontería No
saying that you're going to go to jail or anything
digo que vas a entrar preso ni nada por
like that but it's not nonsense it's a
el estilo pero una tontería no es es un
pain  it
dolor de
's a pain in the ass to
huevos es un dolor de huevos que le
report him
denuncie
because he has videos of him admitting that he
porque tiene vídeos él reconociendo que
took her phone and recorded I don't
le ha cogido el móvil ha registrado no
know what I don't know to what extent they
sé qué no sé hasta qué punto eso te
can condemn you for that, the truth is I
pueden condenar por eso la verdad me
imagine it will depend on the
imagino que dependerá de la
situation I understand that if the
situación Yo entiendo que si las
conversations are about
conversaciones tratan sobre
him I think not the truth is I think
él Creo que no la verdad yo creo que no
nothing happens to him for that
le pasa nada por esa
complaint Hi Javi you already talked about the
denuncia Hola Javi ya hablaste del tema
Comanche the millor issue No now we'll
del Comanche el millor No ahora lo
see it let's see it as a little princess who has been
vemos vamos a verlo de princesita que ha
wasted little princess
estado vasada princesita
eh let's continue second stay with
eh sigamos segundo mantenerme con
wankers And why the streams I do
pajeros Y por qué los streams que hago
in a sweatshirt have the same numbers this
en sudadera tengo lo mismos números esto
is objectively a lie and this This is
es objetivamente mentira y esto Esto es
objectively true And if you want I
objetivamente verdad Y si quieres te lo
'll
vuelvo a
show it to you again is that he always attacks with the
enseñar es que siempre ataca con lo
same thing no So it's like quite easy
mismo no Entonces es como bastante fácil
to
de
disprove
desmentir
we can see this tweet again where
podemos ver otra vez este tweet donde
objectively I have more viewers my
objetivamente tengo más expectadores mi
average viewers increase when I
media de espectadores incrementa cuando
use something that is not obviously
uso un algo que no es obviamente
sexualizing Which I repeat again I don't
sexualizando Que vuelvo a repetir no
think using scotten Stream is
creo que usar scotten Stream sea
sexualizing to sexualize me to
sexualize para sexualizar me para
begin with if I wanted to sexualize myself I
empezar si yo quisiera sexualizar me me
would create an l fans I don't have only fans  I'm
crearía un l fans no tengo only fans
never going to have only fans because I don't
nunca voy a tener only fans porque no
want to live off of sexualize And you know
quiero vivir de sexualize Y sabes
perfectly well that if I were only fans I
perfectamente que si yo me qui fans
could make a lot of money let's continue
podría hacer mucho dinero sigamos
second Why did the places send me this let's see
segundo Por qué me ha mandado esto el
how we
lugares a ver cómo le
explain to her Oh look, these are Lali and
explicamos Ah mira estas son Lali y
Ricky criticizing Princessita someone
Ricky criticando a Princesita alguien se
was running out of viewers and
estaba quedando sin espectadores y ha
had to pull out a really heavy controversy
tenido que tirar de polémica pesada de
Luckily summer is just
[__] Menos mal que el verano está a
around the corner and there's a
la vuelta de la esquina y hay oferta de
pushup offer in sh it made me really sad to
pushup en sh que me daba mucha pena
have to watch her live off
tener que verla vivir de las
Math let's see how we explain to her that
Matemáticas a ver cómo le explicamos que
I'm about to finish my degree and
yo estoy a punto de acabar la carrera y
the other one will be buying bras
la otra se estará comprando sujetadores
and underwear for LoL with the money
y ropa interior para LoL con el dinero
from the impact that he himself has
de la repercusión que él mismo le ha
given her oh my god
dado madre mía de mi
how life must be for you to
vida cómo tiene que estar la vida para
need to break your nerves
que necesita te reviente los piños
dude how it must
tío cómo tiene que
be how you have to
estar cómo tienes que
be how you how you have to be for
estar cómo te cómo tienes que estar para
Princessita to break your nerves
que princesita Te reviente los piños
dude
tío
Princessita the other day I was
princesita que el otro día estaba
saying that you simply are there in
sando que tú simplemente de está allí en
Andorra for are there
andorra por está allí
you spend time there and you go you learn
tú echa tiempo allí y va vas aprendiendo
you acquire
vas adquiriendo el
Catalan  that hurt me even me no no no no
Catalán eso me ha dolido hasta mí no no
this is
no no es que esto es
strong
fuerte
Ah this is the video that luare sent me
Ah este es el vídeo que me ha mandado
damn Ricky in the end it wasn't me who
luare ostia Ricky que al final no fui yo
created it but she is like this
creó pero está
like abusing him not a
como está como abusando de él no un
little bit damn he
poco
's pissing off
[__] se está ceando
eh that your
eh que a tu
girlfriend Look look look
novia Mira mira
Dani a
mira Dani un
kiss some of you need to show your
beso algunas necesitáis enseñar las
chetas and look what I was telling her here
chetas y mira lo que le decía aquí
princess eh I'm not going to shut you up
princesita eh no te voy a callar
I will shut you up time
yo te callará el tiempo
damn when Princess gets them
ostias cuando a Princesita le salen le
they harass her daily nobody says anything
hacen acoso a diario nadie dice nada
now that she's enjoying it because
ahora que se lo está gozando porque el
Karma has acted and she deserves to enjoy it
Karma ha actuado y se merece disfrutar
Oh princess How
Ay princesita Qué
annoying and
pesada y
here here she talks about misogyny But
aquí aquí habla de misoginia Pero por
why are you talking about misogyny here if you
qué hablas aquí de misoginia si se
two girls are fighting and almost
estáis peleando dos tía y casi todo el
everyone is giving the
mundo le está dando caña a
other one a hard time the kid 15 video of almost an
a la otra el pibe 15 vídeo de casi una
hour each the people are mad based on me
hora cada uno la peña padreada basado yo
15 tweet the people yes Paula yes no it
15 tweet la peña que sí Paula que sí no
's that at that moment at that moment
es que en ese momento en ese momento
Well it looked bad princess it was  bad What's
Pues quedó mal princesita quedó mal Qué
going on well what's going on is
es lo que pasa pues lo que pasa es
[Music]
[Música]
what's going on is that
que lo que pasa es que
e
e
m has turned around he has turned around
m se ha dado la vuelta se ha dado la
Agustín 51 recognizes Javi
vuelta Agustín 51 reconoce a Javi
Oliveira and criticizes the other
oliveira y critica a los demás canales
gossip channels day but I felt like
salseo día pero me ha apetecido
starting it in a different way and I
empezarlo de una manera diferente y he
said why am I not going to pay for the PC I'm
dicho por qué no voy a pagar el PC me
going to stay quiet here for 2 minutes
voy a quedar callado aquí 2 minutos
Of course I do I curse
Claro que sí me cago en
God forgive me guys God is not to
Dios perdonadme chicos Dios no tiene la
blame Hey God bless us all which
culpa Eh Dios nos bendiga a todos que
by the way is incredible because I see that
por cierto es increíble porque veo que
the good one no what the [ __ ] am I going to talk
el bueno no qué [__] voy a hablar yo
about sociopolitics here and lastly dude
aquí de sociopolítica ya lo último tío
what I was missing now I'll save that
lo que me faltaba ya eso ya me lo guardo
for dinner with my friends and at
para la cena con los colegas y como
most I'll save it if I meet up with
muchísimo me lo guardo si quedo con
your cousin the lame one you know what I
vuestra prima la coja sabes lo que te
want to tell you I'm going to get here to
quiero decir voy a poner yo aquí a
talk about sociopolitics now suddenly
hablar de sociopolítica ahora de repente
that if I have crossed my wires I'm
que si me se me han cruzado los cables
going to start talking about well well well well well
me voy a poner hablar de bueno bueno
shut up
bueno bueno bueno cállate
shut up I'm trying to find out about the
cállate estoy intentando enterarme del
[ __ ] starving man who lives off your
[__] muerto de hambre que vive de tu
[ __ ] image brother my mother of love
[__] imagen hermano madre mía del amor
beautiful I've realized lately
hermoso me he dado cuenta últimamente
that it doesn't even bother me that they live off my
que ya ni me cabrea que vivan de mi
image, even if they got their sausage, he
imagen incluso conseguido su salchicha
even idolizes me, the truth is he
incluso me idolatra la verdad me
idolizes me that they live off my image, I've been
idolatra que vivan de mi imagen lo he
thinking about it and it's like [ __ ] well
estado pensando y es como [__] pues
Chio mouth of but it's that it is like that or rather it's
Chío boca de pero es que es así o sea es
literally Yes it is like that I mean that
que literalmente Sí es
people talk to see the
así O sea que la gente hable a ver lo
first thing to live to live off his image Nobody lives,
primero vivir vivir de su imagen No vive
he simply makes
simplemente él pues da muchos titulares
a lot of headlines, I mean the gossip channels are like a medium literally we are a medium that we go around echoing the things that happen during the day in this case of gossip okay in telesalseo in my telesalseo channel well, TV news the ratings This program is closed this one opens this collaborator fights with another one anyway okay okay like for example
otro en fin vale vale como por ejemplo
the football channels there is not the
los canales que hay de fútbol no está el
channel of this kid that I get along very
canal de este chaval que yo me llevo muy
well called Víctor Palacio
bien que se llama Víctor Palacio
mancer also they are not channels that talk
mancer también no son canales que hablan
about football news and each one has
de noticias del fútbol y cada uno tiene
an opinion because in fact I think that
una opinión porque de hecho creo que
Víctor has a completely
Víctor tiene una opinión completamente
different opinion than for example mancer on
diferente a la de por ejemplo mancer en
many topics, I don't  I do a lot of football
muchos temas yo no hago muchoo de fútbol
but everyone has their own thing.
pero cada uno tiene su Bueno le tira más
One thing attracts more than another and nothing happens
una cosa a otra y y no pasa nada
as long as you're not disrespectful but it's
mientras que no te falta respeto pero es
good that you're in Boca Juniors. I
bueno que estés en Boca de la gente O
mean, imagine if nobody talked about
sea imagínate que nadie hablase de
Cristiano
Cristiano
Ronaldo. Imagine if nobody talked about
Ronaldo Imagínate que nadie hablase de
Ronaldo. I don't know, I myself. I prefer to
Ronaldo yo no lo yo yo me yo prefiero a
simply see that if there's
ver yo simplemente el que el que si hay
someone who says something
alguien que dice algo que falta el
disrespectful or that is actionable, then you
respeto o que es demandable pues lo
sue them without further ado. But let them talk about
demandas sin más vale pero que hablen de
you and make videos of you saying, "
ti y que saquen vídeos de que tú digas
I'm going to the Chinese store to buy a Red Bull."
me voy al chino a comprarme un Red Bull
That's good, it's not interesting. That's good,
Eso es bueno interesa no Eso es bueno
of course, it's a compliment. What
claro es que es un halago es que lo que
people don't understand is that it's a compliment.
la gente no entiende que eso es un alago
There are people who get angry and
hay gente que se Raya que se cabrea y
upset because people talk about it and
que se pica porque hablen de ello y
because, for example, I don't give a damn. There are
porque a mí por ejemplo me la suda hay
people who seem really annoying because
gente que me parece muy pesada porque
there are people who, like, only
hay gente que como Solamente le funciona
talk about Javier Oliveira works for them. Well, just, let's
hablar de Javier oliveira Pues solo solo
see if not. Even if Javier is in Puente, they'll
a ver si no Aunque javir esté de Puente
invent something and I'll tell something
pues ya se inventan algo y cuento algo
from 25 years ago.  I know but that you are
de hace 25 años yo que sé pero que seas
skilled in the subject and you only talk about one subject
hábil el tema y solo hablas de un tema
then you say that you only talk
entonces ahí dices tú que solo habla
but that the gossip channels that upload
pero que los canales de salseo que suben
20 videos a day one of them each or rather one
20 vídeos Al Día uno de ellos cada o sea
of those videos every two weeks is it
uno de esos vídeos cada dos semanas eres
you or every week well I don't see you living off of
tú o cada semana pues no lo veo vivir de
you I see that you are just another headline and it's
ti lo veo que eres un titular más y está
okay that you appear there I don't know I don't
bien que aparezcas ahí No lo sé no lo
see it as bad bad of people who aren't worth a
veo mal malo de gente que no vale un
penny and who have to talk about others
duro y que tiene que hablar de los demás
negatively to be able to eat [ __ ] and
negativamente para poder comer [__] y
tell their mother that they live off their dream you
decirle a su madre que vive de su sueño
know your dream was to be a Call
sabes tu sueño era ser youtuber de Call
of Duty youtuber that I know
of Duty que lo sé
your dream was to be what
yo tu sueño era ser lo que éramos
we were you have become this
nosotros te has convertido en esto
because there was no way for your
porque es que no había manera de que tu
content to ever become what you
contenido llegara en ningún momento a
wanted it to be no if not you
ser lo que querías que fuera no si no no
wouldn't have been a content creator of
hubieses sido un creador de contenido de
salt That's how it is do
sal Eso es así
n't listen to me listen to me listen to me
no escúchame escúchame escúchame
escame
escame
Look at Twitter Javi why would I look at
Mira Twitter Javi para qué voy a mirar
Twitter you idiot I'm on YouTube
Twitter [__] estoy en YouTube
listen to me specify there are
escúchame especifica que hay gente
short people no let's see I understand what you
cortita no a ver yo entiendo que se
mean there are some youtubers  about gossip
refiere hay algunos youtubers de salseo
I've already said nothing bad either I mean
yo ya lo he dicho nada malo tampoco O
I don't say it in a way With all due
sea yo no lo digo de manera Con todo el
respect in the world I mean there are creators
respeto del mundo O sea hay creadores
who have wanted to be creators of well
que han querido ser creadores de pues
like them of playing here playing in this
como ellos de jugar aquí jugar en esta
series playing there no no matter what I mean it's not
serie jugar allí no no pasa nada O sea
bad at all but
no es nada malo pero
well you don't always get lucky in
bueno no siempre se tiene suerte en
all the content I know many
todos los contenidos yo conozco muchos
youtubers eh I mean not only about
youtubers eh o sea no solamente de
gossip of I mean I know many
salseos de o sea yo conozco muchos
youtubers that that talk about topics
youtubers que que que hablan de temas
that maybe haven't been their passion it's not
que a lo mejor no han sido su pasión no
that they dislike gossip either it's not that they don't
es que le disguste tampoco el salseo no
dislike it either
es que le no es que le disguste tampoco
but it's not the main content I mean it's
pero no es el contenido principal O sea
not the one But it can be a springboard
no es el que Pero puede ser un trampolín
Hey if it hasn't worked for me This has
Oye si no me ha funcionado Esto me ha
worked for me well this Hey in the end Hey in the
funcionado esto pues Oye al final Oye al
end the business is like this I mean but
final el negocio es así O sea pero
how many people don't have to work
cuánta gente no tiene que trabajar que
I tell you in jobs that they don't like
te digo yo en trabajos que no le gustan
how many people surely many of here Well maybe you do
cuánta gente seguro que muchos de aquí
n't dislike it and you're doing
Pues a lo mejor no te disgusta y te va
well and youo I had you positioned
bien y youo tuve te posicionado
this when when when
esto cuando
the whole thing came out this
cuando cuando salió todo el tema este
Antonio David Rosito and others
Antonio David rosito y demás salieron
heart channels came out but well you know
canales del corazón pero bueno sabes
Well but if it works for you and gives you money
Bueno pero si te funciona y te da pasta
how are you going? Ah well no because no
cóm lo vas que Ah pues no porque no
because I wanted Call of Duty if it's
porque yo quería Call of Duty si te está
giving you money then well you'll keep
dando pasta pues lo pues lo seguirás
doing it It's
haciendo No pasa
okay As I always say e Antonio Thank you very much
nada Como siempre digo e Antonio Muchas
for the 21st month subscription and
gracias por el 21o mes de suscripción y
to Dani too for Prime I
a Dani también por el Prime te lo
really appreciate it the truth everything everything
agradezco mucho la verdad todo que todo
everyone at least the ones I see except
todos al menos los que yo veo excepto
Look look where it is Salty Quite a lot
Mira fíjate por donde se Salado bastante
Javi Oliveira Because Javi Oliveira is a
Javi oliveira Porque Javi oliveira es un
kid who creates gossip content
chaval que crea contenido de salseo
since I knew him because that's what I I am yes I
desde que yo lo conozco por qué es lo
love it, I mean
que me Yo es que si lo amo
I do love it the gossip I mean I love it I love it I love it I love it I mean I like
o sea yo es que sí lo amo el salseo O
the gossip I mean I
o sea el chisme me gusta o sea yo lo
live it eh I live it I think that it
vivo eh yo lo vivo yo creo que eso
also shows in part eh Sofia a
también en parte se nota eh Sofía un
kiss sweetheart
beso corazón
gorgeous mm we're not going to get there question
guapísimo mm no vamos a llegar pregunta
eh question ask now the jacket I don't care
eh pregunta pregunta ya la chaqueta me
the jacket is not in the
da igual la chaqueta no está en el
catalog I don't care okay well I don't care
catálogo me da igual vale bueno no me da
you should look for it but HM
igual deberíais buscarla pero HM
apart from the jacket issue apart from the issue
aparte del tema chaqueta aparte del tema
jacket but he didn't say he didn't see me that's a
chaqueta pero no dijo que no te veía eso
lie everyone sees me they've
es mentira todo el mundo me ve me han
stopped me even in Oporto a kiss guys
parado hasta en oporto un beso chavales
who stopped me in Oporto and in Vigo too they
que me pararon en oporto y en vigo
also greeted me in Vigo
también también me saludaron en vigo
listen to me
escúchame
mm about the jacket okay it's not in
mm que lo de la chaqueta vale no está en
the
el
catalog members can reach
catálogo los miembros podemos llegar a
3000 I ask I ask I ask
3000 pregunto
eh I ask I ask can we
pregunto pregunto eh pregunto pregunto
stop being the shame of
podemos dejar de ser la vergüenza de
YouTube I ask eh I ask eh you
YouTube pregunto eh pregunto eh ustedes
can answer me whatever you want
me podéis contestar lo que queráis
eh Javi I don't know if you've already talked about this
eh Javi No sé si ya hablaste de esto
but it is said out there that Lali already had
pero se dice por ahí que Lali ya tenía
an l a while ago but with another
un l de hace un tiempo pero con otro
name and I only sold privately that's why
nombre y solo vendí en privado por eso
nobody knew and nothing had been leaked
nadie sabía ni se había filtrado
nothing has reached me soul
nada no me ha llegado nada alma Muchas
Thank you very much for the
gracias por el
contribution ungrateful ungrateful
aporte desagradecido desagradecido
you María José that I am here watching
ustedes María José que estoy aquí viendo
Agustín I am watching Agustín here we
Agustín estoy viendo aquí a Agustín
are here what do I know for you to
estamos aquí yo que sé para que os
become a member Well I don't know but come on it
hagáis miembro Pues no lo sé pero vamos
would be great that eh that hasn't
sería la [__] eso eh a mí eso no me ha
reached me of course but if that's the case it
llegado desde luego peramos si eso es
would be great no it's a Coto But the
así sería la [__] no é un Coto Pero
others  So half known were
los demás Así medio conocidos eran
attempts by creators who got
intentos de creadores que conseguid de
their sausage that didn't
su salchicha que no les llegaba a
quite work for them what they did they
funcionar del todo lo que hacían
had to start talking about others
tuvieron que empezar a hablar de los
to if not no and if not to study to put their
para si no no y si no a empollar a meter
elbows and they didn't want to study they
los codos y ellos no querían empollar
had to of the story but their story didn't
tenían que del cuento pero su cuento no
work So they get into the
funcionaba Así que se meten en los
stories
cuentos
of but because it's so chopped that they
de pero por está tan picado que han
said of
dicho
Thank you very much Tatiana Look Tatiana
de Muchas gracias Tatiana Mira Tatiana
has listened to me man what can't
me ha hecho caso hombre que lo que no
be that you're here for
puede ser que estéis aquí de
nothing
balde
Jai you would love with crybaby 51 well the
Jai te amarías con llorón 51 bueno la
last time he already like asked me half
última vez ya como que me pidió medio
Sorry no good hanger a kiss
Perdón no buena percha un beso Muchas
Thank you very much Look good hanger 20 member How
gracias Mira buen percha 20 miembro Qué
handsome you are good hanger Thank you very much
guapo eres buen percha Muchas gracias
now I'm at peace with Agustín eh I mean now I
ya yo estoy en paz con Agustín eh o sea
'm at peace with Agustín and with
ya est estoy en paz con Agustín y con
the other gossip right now I don't have
los otros del salseo no tengo ahora
any problem with
mismo ningún problema con
anyone well let's see he kind of
nadie bueno a ver él como que medio Se
apologized it doesn't sound to me that he apologized not
disculpó no me suena que se disculpó no
in the little of the delos not for mine and such
en el poca del delos no por lo mío y tal
and and that we're doing well it doesn't sound to me
y y que vamos bien no me suena
Don't listen to me But okay  you see With
No escúchame Pero bueno verás tú Con
all due respect to the I don't know if he's
todo el respeto al a los Es que no sé si
going to say specific names or what
va a decir nombre en concretos o qué
but they've dedicated themselves to what they wanted to have
pero que se han dedicado al que querían
dedicated themselves to I know creating
haberse dedicado a yo que sé a crear
content playing and such And then they got into
contenido jugando y tal Y luego les ha
gossip Well it's okay it's
ido el salseo bueno no pasa
okay but let's see what What do I
nada no pasa nada pero a ver que Qué
do if suddenly by gossiping I have I
hago si de repente haciendo salseo tengo
don't know how many millions of
no sé cuántos millones de visitas
monthly visits and I earn I don't know how much and I can
mensuales y gano no sé cuánto y puedo
work quietly on something that I
trabajar tranquilito en algo que me
like Doesn't mean that you dislike them I
gusta no quiere decir que te disgusten o
mean the fact that you
sea el hecho de que a ti mejor te
would have rather been a more
hubiera gustado ser un youtuber más
mainstream youtuber not one of those series and
mainstream no de estos de series y de
games and all that but then what you've gotten into
juegos y demás pero luego lo que te ha
is gossip and it's making you a lot of
resulta es el salseo y te está dando una
money and you don't dislike it either I mean it doesn't
pasta y tampoco te disgusta O sea no
mean that you
quiere decir que te
dislike kitun Thanks a lot man it
disguste kitun Muchas gracias hombre
would maybe be a [ __ ] that you don't
sería a lo mejor una putada que no te
like gossip and you do it because it's the
guste el salseo y lo hagas porque sea lo
only thing you like But if you like it too it's okay
único que te va Pero si también te gusta
not incredible Why do I say this Well I don't
no increíble Por qué digo esto Pues no
know because I'm in a bad mood and went to the
sé porque estoy de mala [__] y ido al
gym I had sore muscles bro and I couldn't man I
gy tenía agujeta hermano y no podía tío
couldn't or to the gym I had  sore and I haven't
no podía o al gy tenía agujeta y no he
made the marks that I wanted to make I haven't
hecho las marcas que quería hacer no he
made my PR my personal Records bro I haven't
hecho mis PR mi personal Records bro no
done them t I have marked my personal
los he hecho t me he marcado mi personal
Records, it's already
Records ya
the truth Why lie Well
está la verdad Para qué engañar Bueno
one more dude not of the day no How many
pues un cío más no del día no Cuántos
cameos have I had during the weekend
cameos habré tenido durante el fin
How many cameos have I had during the
de Cuántos cameos he tenido durante el
weekend while I have not been here tell me
finde mientras que no he estado contadme
Hey hey hey hey
Oye oye oye oye
Sofia has given away 10 members
que Sofía ha regalado 10 miembros
too eh What's up
también eh Qué pasa
eh listen Sofia has given away 10 members it's
eh escucha Sofía ha regalado 10 miembro
worth it eh you want it a
ya os vale eh que lo queréis
gift Javi the dude insulted you
regalito Javi el moror te insultó
yesterday the dude insulted me yesterday Oh well
ayer el moror me insultó ayer
nothing It's that of course it's really funny to me
nada Es que claro me hace mucha gracia
when I go live he says Have you seen
cuando entro en directo dice Has visto
the thread they did to you Have you seen the
el hilo que te han hecho has visto el
live they did to you yesterday the
directo que te han hecho ayer me insultó
dude insulted me Why why did he
el millor Por
insult me ​​because he doesn't rest yesterday you had
insultó porque no descansa ayer tuviste
a cameo with utv
con utv un
what's new let's see the dude in
cameo qué novedad a ver lo del millor en
honor of the truth
honor a la verdad
eh someone put it to me in an email that he
eh alguien me lo puso en un email que me
had insulted me no that he started like
había insultado no que se ha puesto como
watching videos now of Dallas and
a ver vídeos ahora de Dallas y de wimu y
of wimu and those fights no and in a video there was me and him and the moror started telling me that I was a rat I was like I was a rat that went around here there no something like that no I don't remember but they told me in an
dijeron en un
email what can I say to you what do I know to me the
email qué te digo yo que sé a m el
best is that he seems like a
millor es que me parece una
person I don't think he's a very
persona no me parece una persona muy
intelligent person right he is a
inteligente verad es una persona
short person Sofia a kiss let's see what I can tell you that
cortilla Sofía un beso a ver qué te digo
the best insults me and what am I
yo que me insulta el millor y yo que le
going to answer? Oh well you plus me rat
voy a responder Ah pues tú más yo rata
Well you plus you fool Well you plus what do you
Pues tú más tú tonto Pues tú más qué te
V if he is the best anyway it's some guy who comes
V si es el millor sea es un tío que se
up with it it's some guy who comes up with it
le ocurre es un tío que se le ocurre
living in another country to pay
viviendo en otro país para pagar
taxes to [ __ ] and make a video
impuestos [__] y hacer un vídeo
insulting the police or whatever what can I
insultando a la policía o sea qué te
tell you what I'm telling you he's
digo qué Te
too lucky to be
digo demasiada suerte tiene con que
able to still do live shows after
pueda hacer directos todavía después de
what he did to cristinini
lo que le hizo a cristinini
eh but if it's that I imagine it
eh pero si es que yo me imagino que le
hurts him because I tell him that like let's see what I can tell you
dolerá porque le digo eso como a ver qué
if it's the
te digo si es que es la
truth I don't know I don't know let's see I was
verdad no sé no sé a ver yo estuve
watching no I wasn't  watching I have to
viendo no no estuve viendo lo tengo que
watch it
ver
now we'll watch it later we'll watch it
ahora lo vemos luego lo vemos
later
luego
because we're going to see the thing about
porque vamos a ver lo
because we're going to see the thing about Comanche
de porque vamos a ver lo de Comanche
obviously on tiktok this clip is
evidentemente en tiktok este clip es
viral in it you can allegedly see
viral en él se ve presuntamente a
someone similar to Adri Contreras
alguien similar a Adri Contreras
hooking up with the one who Apparently is
liándose con la que Aparentemente es
gemita this is the after of the
gemita esto es el after de la
Queen
Queen
laa is like the one who calls gemer but the
laa es como la que lleva gemer pero el
boy Although he looks a lot like it it could
chico Aunque si se parece mucho podría
not be Adri Contreras let's
no ser Adri Contreras a
see [ __ ] she s she
ver [__] ella s
is she is he I just can't place him [ __ ] I don't know the people who follow him will know him No she yes it is her yes it is clear Uh well recently let's see what people say because it is supposed that she is with an Andorra player Adri Contreras lives in
Adri Contreras vive en
Andorra let's see I know that we saw
andorra a ver yo sé que vimos hace
recently I know that we saw recently like a
poco Yo sé que vimos hace poco como un
live that she was doing and in
eh directo que ella estaba haciendo y en
the live that she was
el directo que ella estaba
doing she says over here it is not Adri
haciendo dice por aquí no es Adri
Contreras Adri was wearing the
Contrera Adri llevaba la camiseta del
Malaga shirt as if he couldn't change it
Málaga como si no se la pudiera cambiar
to go out to
para salir de
party
fiesta
Well she was like talking to someone
Bueno ella como que hablaba con alguien
and telling someone to shut up do you remember
y mandaba callar a alguien os acordáis
that  I mean it was a live show that we saw
de eso o sea fue un directo que vimos
she was doing a live show and she was
ella estaba haciendo un directo y ella
telling someone who was in
mandaba a callar a alguien que estaba en
the house to be quiet okay why did she tell him to be quiet
la casa vale por qué lo mandaba a callar
Because it's probably a voice that
Porque seguramente sea una voz que la
people can recognize if it's the voice of
gente pueda reconocer si es una voz de
someone that no one is going to recognize she doesn't
alguien que nadie va reconocer no lo
tell him to be quiet it doesn't matter you
manda a callar da igual me
know what I mean and you could tell it was like a
entiendes y se notaba que era como un
fling or a boyfriend by the way she
rollete o un novio por la forma en la
addressed him and the laughter and so on no matter what it
que se dirigió a él y la risa y demás no
could be this guy Well it could
que podría ser este chico Pues podría
be the truth it could be clear let's see
ser la verdad podría ser claro a ver
she is eh she is but come on there are
ella es eh ella es pero vamos aquí hay
Peña here who know it So this
Peña que lo sabe O sea que esto
will end up
terminará
coming out sooner rather than later because there
saliendo más pronto que tarde porque ahí
are a lot of people in that
hay un montón de gente en ese
private room and in the private room Not
reservado y en el reservado Tampoco
everyone can get in I understand no
puede acceder cualquiera entiendo no
no let's see the moror thing to see the
no a ver lo del moror para ver lo del
moror thing I think we should
moror yo creo que deberíamos
see the Comanche thing
ver lo de Comanche
no to see the millor thing I think we should
no para ver lo del millor yo creo que
see the
habría que ver lo del
Comanche thing who uploaded a video Why did I
Comanche que ha subido un vídeo Por qué
leave no we should see it no 11
me fui no habría que verlo no 11
minutes let's go
minutillos vamos a
see it
verlo
eye
ojo
the images that you will see below
las imágenes que verás a continuación
are merely illustrative and for
son meramente ilustrativas y con fines
artistic purposes  promote information that
artísticos para promover información que
can help understand
puede ayudar a entender las enfermedades
mental illness at no time with the
mentales en ningún momento con las
scenes filmed is intended to ridicule
escenas rodadas se pretende ridiculizar
or make fun of the subject at hand This
o tomar a burla el tema a tratar de Este
footage is
metraje
okay Hello My name is Carlos and a
vale Hola Mi nombre es Carlos y hace un
month ago I tried to commit suicide
mes intenté suicidarme
But before getting to that we need to
Pero antes de llegar a eso necesitamos
go back a little further but it's true or
retroceder un poco más pero es verdad o
rather what's said is true it's not an
sea lo que cuenta es verdad no es una
experience that he's had
vivencia que ha tenido
[Music]
[Música]
no
no
Kevin Yes that's real and that's Adri yes
Kevin Si eso es real y ese es Adri si
this is real and it's Adri there's going to be trouble
esto es real y es Adri se va a liar
because I understood that Adri had a
porque tenía entendido que Adri tenía
girlfriend maybe I'm sure she'll say something
novia igual estoy seguro que algo dir
tomorrow at the after Kings because she
mañana en el after Kings que a pque le
likes gossip XD okay okay m wait not
gusta el salseo XD vale vale m espera no
so much fast forward One more year there it is Come
tanto adelántale Un año más ahí está Ven
to that Comanche over there That's my
a ese Comanche de ahí Ese es mi yo del
2014 self in that year I was diagnosed with
2014 en ese año fui diagnosticado con
two mental disorders
dos trastornos mentales trastorno
bipolar disorder and manic
bipolar y trastorno maníaco
depression between 2014 and 2018 I was
depresivo entre 2014 y 2018 estuve
hospitalized several times in
internado varias veces en hospitales
psychiatric hospitals and taking medication
psiquiátricos y tomando medicamentos
until one day there was a small
hasta que un día hubo una pequeña
hope of light in my life
esperanza de luz en mi vida
Twitch at the end of 2018 I found  a
Twitch a finales de 2018 encontré una
life motivation to do live streams I
motivación de vida hacer directos Me
loved it I was very excited about everything
encantaba estaba muy ilusionado por todo
that being a streamer entailed besides I
lo que conllevaba ser streamer aparte me
had become friends with one of my
había convertido en amigo de uno de mis
favorite youtubers That's right
youtubers favoritos Así es
Fernan
Fernan
there I didn't know that Comanche had been
ahí no sabía yo que Comanche había sido
friends with Fernan flo damn I have never seen them
amigo de Fernan flo [__] No los he visto
together in my [ __ ] life eh Let's see manche I
juntos en la [__] vida eh A ver manche
met him
lo conocí
since I was invited to the
desde desde que me invitaron a lo del
squid game there he followed me I
juego del calamar ahí él me siguió yo lo
followed him back you know and I know that he is friends
seguí de vuelta sabes y sé que es amigo
with Ari no that he was very good friends with Ari
de de Ari no que era muy amigo de Ari
Gameplay I was very happy I felt that my
Gameplay estaba muy feliz sentía que mi
life finally had meaning and direction I knew
vida por fin tenía sentido y rumbo sabía
what I wanted to do so I made two
lo que quería hacer así que tomé dos
bad decisions one turned out very well and the
malas decisiones una salió muy bien y la
other Well not so
otra Pues no
much I decided to get out of that
tanto decidí salirme de la
was the one that turned out well and also to
Esa fue la que salió bien y también
put aside my treatment for my
dejar de lado mi tratamiento para mis
disorders anyway I was no longer
trastornos de todas formas ya no estaba
sad I didn't need pills or
triste no necesitaba ni de pastillas ni
psychologists and psychiatrists there is a mistake
de psicólogos y psiquiatras hay error el
mine the bad thing is that it took me
mío lo malo es que tardé en darme cuenta
years to realize from 2018 to 2021 everything was going very
años desde 2018 hasta 2021 todo iba muy
well with the streams I had gained a
bien con los streams había ganado una
small base of followers and I had a
pequeña base de Seguidores y tenía una
small but  very nice community and
pequeña pero muy bonita comunidad y ya
the effort of my work on
se notaba el esfuerzo de mi trabajo en
the networks was already noticeable so much so that I made the
las redes tanto así que tomé la decisión
most important decision of my life to move to
más importante de mi vida mudarme a
Mexico mother where was I
México madre de dónde era en un
originally from Javi have you heard what
principio Javi has escuchado lo que ha
Misha said about the boy who
dicho misha del chaval que ha
disappeared in Seville no Cristian what did he
desaparecio en Sevilla no Cristian qué
say he doesn't have a single piece of furniture he doesn't even have a
ha dicho no tiene ni un mueble no tiene
table but after that everything
ni una mesa pero después de eso Todo
changed a lot of good things happened like being
cambió pasaron muchas cosas buenas como
able to visit Europe to
poder visitar Europa para por primera
appear in the
vez aparecer en el
rewine for the first time Here I am here I am here I am That's
rewine Aquí estoy aquí estoy aquí estoy
me doing an event with two of the
yo hacer un evento con dos de los del
biggest Salvadoran youtubers that I
Salvador youtubers más grandes que
admire one person gets it you
admiro se los queda una persona has
said you said 10000 100000 100 s Yes
dicho has dicho 10000 100000 100 s Sí
100000 100000 sorry yes the 100000
100000 100000 perdón sí los 100000 se
goes to one person
los lleva una sola persona
000 of I mean I think it's the biggest prize
000 de o sea creo que es el premio más
that's going to be given in the history
gordo que que se va a dar en la historia
of Twitch eh person
de Twitch eh persona nunca se ha dado
something like this has never happened in a it's an outrage I mean
algo así en un es una barbaridad o sea
whoever wins and takes
el que gane y se lleve
[Music]
[Música]
000  100,000 turkeys that Oli took
000 100000 pavos que se llevó el Oli
eh but the funas also happened that we
eh pero también pasaron las funas que ya
all
todos
[Music]
[Música]
know about. The funas also happened that we
conocemos también pasaron las funas que
all know about but for those who don't
ya todos conocemos pero los que no
know and are about to find out
conocen y que están a punto de conocer
is how these funas affected a
es cómo afectaron estas funas a una
person with a psychological disorder to the
persona con trastorno psic lógicos al
point of almost leading him to death
punto de casi llevarlo a la muerte
after a few months of being one of the
después de unos meses siendo una de las
most hated people on the internet or at
personas más odiadas de internet o al
least that's how I felt from my
menos así es que lo sentía yo desde mi
point of view having a shitty year
punto de vista teniendo un año de [__]
starting with a chick who tried to farm me to
empezando con una tipa que intentó farme
hook up and the project that I had been
por ligar y el proyecto el cual llevaba
working on for months didn't turn out the way I
trabajando meses no salió como me lo
expected and there were several mistakes because of me
esperaba Y tuvo varios errores por mi
that I even ended up making a
culpa que hasta terminé haciendo el
fool of myself in a stupid fight with Sprint
ridículo en una pelea tonta con Sprint
until I was diagnosed with
hasta que me diagnosticaron una
thrombosis a very serious illness that
trombosis una enfermedad muy grave que
after going to the
para después de ir al partido de
youtubers game a very, very viral tweet came out
youtubers saliera un tweet muy pero muy
criticizing my image and my physique
viral criticando mi imagen y mi físico
Oh the one that went viral of calling him a
Ah el que se hizo viral de diciéndole
dog
perro
no the dog thing no like it
no lo del perro no así
was back then where I was already very
como fue en ese entonces en donde ya muy
mentally affected
afectado mental
How beautiful I gave birth man at the end of the year I'm going to
Qué bonito parí tío en fin de año voy a
go to Paris again I think I decided  give myself
ir otra vez a París yo creo decidí darme
a break and made another bad decision
un descanso y tomé otra mala decisión
running away from my problems that's right instead of
huir de mis problemas así es en lugar de
taking advantage of my break and looking for help help that I
ocupar mi descanso y buscar ayuda ayuda
so desperately needed I left Oh
que necesitaba fuertemente me fui Ay
this is London How beautiful man
esto es Londres Qué bonito tío
London How beautiful London was
Londres Qué bonito fue Londres
eh TR through Europe wasting almost all my
eh TR por Europa malgastar casi todo mi
money because I thought that the solution to my
dinero porque creí que la solución a mis
problems was to escape from them but in
problemas era escapar de ellos pero en
reality nothing fulfilled me I was still empty
realidad nada me llenaba seguía vacío
inside until the last straw fell
por dentro hasta que cayó la última gota
the day my
que derramó el vaso el día que me
passport was stolen from Ivisa that day
robaron el pasaporte en ivisa ese día
was where I exceeded my limit his
fue donde sobrepase mi límite le robaron
passport was stolen from
el pasaporte en
Ivisa I didn't understand Why didn't
ivisa no entendía Por qué no no paraban
things kept happening to me
de pasarme cosas
[Music]
[Música]
bad my head had exploded I was
malas mi cabeza había explotado era otro
completely different I wanted to hurt myself and I
completamente me quería hacer daño y
wanted to hurt people I
quería hacer daño también a personas que
loved too I went completely crazy I had
quería me volví completamente loco tuve
to leave the holiday villa for
que abandonar la villa de vacaciones por
the sake of my friends and mine and me How did he
el bien de mis amigos y el mío y me Cómo
say listen you're listening to this
ha dicho escucha está escuchando esto
I had to leave I
tuve que abandonar
wanted to hurt myself and the
me quería hacer daño a mí mismo y a la
people I loved I mean surely this
gente que quería o sea seguramente esto
means that there was an episode of
quiere decir que hubo un episodio de de
back and forth
ida de
hoa back and forth with someone the
hoa de ida de olla con alguien la villa
holiday villa for the sake of my friends
de vacaciones por el bien de mis amigos
and mine and  I went to lock myself in a hotel
y el mío y me fui a encerrar en un hotel
in Madrid where I tried to commit
en Madrid en donde ahí intenté
suicide without any success. I was so
suicidarme sin éxito alguno estaba tan
mentally affected that I barely know
afectado mentalmente que apenas y sé
how I managed to return to my
cómo le hice para regresar aa de mis
parents in El Salvador. For me it all happened
padres en El Salvador Para mí fue todo
in the blink of an eye. Once in
en un abrir y cerrar de ojos una vez en
El Salvador I spent one of the most
El Salvador pasé uno de los meses más
horrible months of my life and when I arrived I
horribles de mi vida y es que llegando
locked myself in my room so I couldn't
me encerré en mi habitación para no
leave. I
salir de
spent a whole month feeling the
ahí pasé un mes entero sintiendo los
horrors of all my disorders. By
horrores de todos mis trastornos que por
the way, I told you that in 2014 I
cierto si te dije que en 2014 tenía
only had two disorders.
solamente dos trastornos recientemente
I recently took another test and it turned out that I have
me hice otro test y resultó que tengo
more than cco different disorders. Now I
más de cco trastornos distintos Ahora
want you to imagine what it's like to be
quiero que imagines lo que es estar
locked up for a whole month in a
encerrado por un mes entero en una
room that's 4 by 3. Met and if you can't,
habitación de 4 por 3 Met y si no puedes
then let me.
pues déjame
Rattan contributed greatly to the
ratán contribuyeron en gran parte a las
funas that led me to hit rock
funas que me llevaron a tocar
bottom. First of all, let's talk about
fondo primero que nada hablemos de la
bipolarity. Why do we have to talk
bipolaridad Por qué tenemos que hablar
about it? Javi has told you about illnesses
de ella Javi te ha dicho enfermedades
that he has and that he stopped taking medication. You
que tiene y y que dejó la medicación te
can have any crisis. I understand, I
puede dar cualquier crisis Entiendo
understand because that's where my
entiendo porque de ahí se derivan mis
other disorders stem from. Basically, it's the root
demás trastornos básicamente es la raíz
of most of my mental problems
de la mayoría de mis problemas mentales
and the driving force behind my other disorders, such as
y el motor de mis demás trastornos como
depression anxiety obsessions
la depresión ansiedad obsesiones
compulsions and schizophrenia But well
compulsiones y esquizofrenia Pero bueno
what is bipolarity bipolarity is not
Qué es la bipolaridad la bipolaridad no
like everyone thinks that
es como todo el mundo piensa sobre que
one day you are happy and the next sad no no no no no no no
un día estás feliz y al otro triste no
this does not work like that
no no no no no no esto no funciona así
bipolarity is more like a
la bipolaridad es más bien como un
catalyst for your emotions that is to say
catalizador de tus emociones es decir
that bipolarity increases all your
que la bipolaridad aumenta todas tus
emotions and for having not only
emociones habidas y por haber no solo la
happiness and sadness it increases your
felicidad y la tristeza aumenta tus
fears your anger your doubts your joys
miedos tus enojos tus dudas tus alegrías
your sexual appetite in short it increases your
tu apetito sexual en fin aumenta tus
feelings or rather all the
sentimientos o más bien toda aquella
emotions that come out of your mind Therefore it
emoción que de tu mente salga Por ende
exponentially increases my other
aumenta exponencialmente mis otros
mental disorders now how is it to
trastornos mentales ahora bien cómo es
live with this well being a streamer is
vivir con esto pues siendo streamer es
the worst thing that can happen to you if you suffer from
lo peor que te puede pasar si sufres de
these disorders Or have you not
estos trastornos O es que Acaso no han
heard the famous saying manches he doesn't
escuchado el tan famoso dicho manches no
know when to stop or Broken Thank you very much
sabe cuándo parar o Broken Muchísimas
friend I'm looking at a little thing eh
amigo Estoy mirando una cosilla eh
guys
chavales
Broken Thank you very much
Broken Muchas gracias
handsome Thank goodness Broken is coming to
guapo Menos mal que viene Broken a
become a member eh thank goodness eh Because
hacerse miembro eh menos mal eh Porque
if it depends on you the 3000 of us are
si depende de usted los 3000 vamos
done
listos
eh Don't stain a horny
eh No manches un
guy and watch out I'm not
cachondo y ojo no le estoy echando la
completely blaming my disorders in
culpa completamente a mis trastornos en
its entirety no no no no no since it
su totalidad no no no no no ya que mi
's also my duty to worry about them and
deber también es preocuparme por ellos y
how they influence my work and I
por cómo influyen en mi trabajo y hace
should have sought help a long time ago and I did
tiempo que debía haber buscado ayuda y
n't until everything went to
no lo hice hasta que todo se fue al
hell but unfortunately many of
[__] pero desgraciadamente muchas de
my funas were caused by impulses that I
mis funas fueron causa de impulsos que
couldn't control thanks to my
no pude controlar gracias a mis
mental disorders to which I didn't
trastornos mentales a los cuales no
pay attention and I regret
atendía tiempo y me arrepiento de
[Music] what a
[Música]
montage more crinch no manche
ello vaya montaje más crinch no manche
imitating a suicide half-naked a
imitando un suicidio semidesnudo un
little bit Yes the truth a little bit like that in
poquillo Sí la verdad un poquillo así en
heat been and that
calon sido y eso
a little bit
un poo
yes showing his fatness but let me
sí enseñando su gordura pero déjame
tell you something and that is that suicide and
decirte algo y es que el suicidio y las
mental illnesses are not at all
enfermedades mentales no son para nada
something cringe in fact they are worrying and
algo cringe de hecho son preocupantes y
I went through all that that you just saw
yo pasé por todo eso que acabas de ver
on screen with failed suicide attempts
en pantalla con intentos de suicidio
thanks to the hate that says sweet
fallidos gracias al hate de dice dulce
Pinky every time you say that it makes
Pinky cada vez que dices eso menos ganas
me feel less like becoming a
me dan de hacerme
member Hey but why do you get
miembro Oye pero por qué te pones
like that Hey but pinki member art You don't feel like it
así Oye pero pinki arte miembro No
Pinky Take a turn Pinky you never wanted to
Pinky Dad una vuelta Pinky no querías
do it I
hacerlo
never thought about you don't blame
nunca no te pensaba no me eches la culpa
me that you don't  you're going to become a
a mí de que tú no te vayas a ser
member you weren't going to do it in any
miembro no te ibas a hacer de ninguna
way the internet and all my
manera internet y todos mis trastornos
mental disorders if you are living a
mentales si estás viviendo una situación
similar situation from here I encourage you to seek
similar desde acá te animo a que busques
help You still have time to do it
ayuda Aún estás a tiempo de hacerlo
And why show myself
Y por qué Mostrarme
half naked because it was a complex That I
semidesnudo porque era un complejo Que
had thanks to the comments on the
tenía gracias a los comentarios de
Internet but now thanks to
Internet pero que ahora gracias a la
therapy I am overcoming after having
terapia estoy superando después de haber
hit rock bottom and as a good friend
tocado fondo y como un buen amigo me
told me once you hit rock bottom you only have to
dijo una vez tocas fondo solo te queda
go up comi So let's go
ir para arriba comi Así que vámonos para
up
arriba
well
bueno
eh Let's see if it's true that the video
eh A ver sí que es verdad que el vídeo
is a little bit like that a little bit like that
es un poquillo así de un poquillo así
cringe not the way it has been done
cringe no la forma que ha tenido hacerlo
and bad but well maybe
y de mal pero bueno igual
eh maybe he's right The kid of course I mean he had a
eh igual tiene razón El chaval claro o
bad time Ramón Ho
sea la la ha pasado mal Ramón Ho no
shouldn't have stopped the medication his
tenía que haber dejado la medicación su
fall was because he believed himself to be God in the squids
caída fue por creerse Dios en los squids
games well eh you can't have a
games bueno eh tú no puedes tener una
roller coaster of emotions if you are
montaña rusa de emociones si tú estás
under treatment and you stop the
bajo tratamiento y te quitas el
treatment on your own eh When you have
tratamiento tu solo eh Cuando te viene
a roller coaster of emotions like something like that
una montaña rusa de emociones como algo
and more on several occasions no eh
así y más en varias ocasiones no eh
projects that big are they if they already are
proyectos así de gordo tienen si ya de
for example I don't  that I'm here
por sí por ejemplo yo no que estoy aquí
247 you already have m roller coasters of
247 ya tienes m montañas rusas de
emotions in the sense of joy
emociones en el sentido de alegría
anger frustration eh stress that
enfado frustración eh agobio que te
overwhelm you because you know like a thousand things no
agobian porque sabes o sea mil cosas no
if you're on medication and you throw it away well of
si tú estás bajo medicación y lo dejas
course that can
por la cara pues claro eso te puede
affect you for the worse it can affect you very
afectar para mal te puede afectar muy
badly the
mal el
best Where is the best now I mean
millor Dónde está el millor ahora o sea
every time you send me now click of the
cada vez que me mandáis ahora click del
best
millor
eh it appears here in another new place I don't
eh aparece aquí en otro sitio nuevo no
know if it's because he's traveling or what But well
sé si es que está de viaje o qué Pero
apparently it's gotten out of hand
bueno por lo visto se ha
because he said some outrage
liado porque ha dicho una barbaridad
[Music]
[Música]
no the images that you'll see below
no las imágenes que verás a continuación
are uploads but I have to see the
son subos pero que tengo que ver la
entire reaction or it's
reacción entera o me la
summarized for me dinners rolled it's intended to
resumidos cenas rodadas se pretende
ridicule discretion time to
ridic discreción tiempo de
save you and 20 gifted sub What the
salvarte y 20 gifted sub What the
[ __ ] this has taken a lot of seriousness off the
fuck esto le ha quitado mucha seriedad
matter oh oh
al asunto ay ay
[Laughter]
[Risas]
you again Hello My name is Carlos and
os de nuevo Hola Mi nombre es Carlos y
a month ago I tried to commit suicide but
hace un mes intenté suicidarme pero
before getting to that we need to
antes de llegar a eso necesitamos
go back a little more okay I'm going to give my
retroceder un poco más vale voy a dar mi
opinion on this subject obviously I'm not
opinión sobre este tema obviamente no
saying that it's the case of Comanche but I
digo que sea el caso de Comanche pero yo
think that  if you try there are two
creo que si intentas hay dos
possibilities either you are completely [ __ ]
posibilidades o eres completamente put
[ __ ] or you are looking for attention there
[__] mental o buscas atención no
are no attempts at sudio unless you are
hay intentos de sudio a no ser que seas
subal [ __ ] dude this
subal [__] tío este
kid [ __ ] dude this kid every time
chaval [__] tío este chaval cada vez
you send me something from this
que me mandáis algo de este
kid And the thing is that he is in the negative of iq
chaval Y es que está en negativo de iq
eh
eh
be it is that he is literally in the negative
sea es que literalmente está en negativo
eh [ __ ] dude I mean but this this
eh [__] putísima tío o sea pero esto
I many times when when you
esto yo muchas veces cuando cuando me
send me a clip of this
mandáis clip de este
man I think that it is like his
hombre Yo pienso que es como su
character exaggerating it no
personaje exagerándolo no
eh but then I say but it is that really
eh pero luego digo pero es que realmente
he has pretty good numbers no I
él tiene bastante buenos números no O
mean he has pretty good numbers
sea él tiene bastante buenos números
playing LoL and things like that no I mean he is
jugando a LoL y esas cosas no O sea él
like [ __ ] [ __ ] he is doing very well I
como que [__] [__] que le va muy bien O
mean he does not need these things I mean it is not
sea no necesit estas cosas o sea no es
like his character to gain fame I do
como su personaje para para ganar fama
not understand I mean he really thinks like that and
no entiendo O sea él piensa así de
and and and he does not process it and and and he knows
verdad y y y y no lo procesa y y y sabe
the way to say it or how to say it or not to say it
la forma de decirlo o cómo decirlo o no
which is also an
decirlo que también es una
option my god
opción madre mía
man It is that every time I have seen something
tío Es que yo cada vez que he visto algo
of these are
de
things that you the things that are no longer
son cosas que tú la cosas que ya no
only the controversy that we have followed
solamente la polémica que hemos seguido
not the controversy that he has had
no la polémica que él ha tenido
with  the controversy he had with
con la polémica que ha tenido con con
Danan, no, the best there, he
danan no que ahí el millor se ha
invented half of it, he leaves episodes in
inventado la mitad se deja episodios por
between and all that, no, good, okay, he could be
medio y todo eso no bueno Vale puede ser
a manipulator and now a guy who starts
un manipulador y ya un tío que se pone a
doing a live stream, see a guy who
hacer un directo a ver un tío que se
starts doing a live stream yelling at his
pone a hacer un directo gritándole a la
ex-girlfriend that she's a [ __ ], [ __ ], a
exnovia que si es una [__] [__] una
[ __ ] [ __ ], his
[__] subnormal a la
ex-girlfriend since 2018 following the king of
exnovia desde 2018 siguiendo al rey del
salsa, kiss bro, my goodness, more than 5 years,
sals beso brok madre mía más de 5 años
a kiss, a kiss,
un beso un beso
gorgeous, I mean, the thing with Cristinini
guapísimo o sea es que lo de cristinini
was already, for me, the image of the best,
ahí ya fue para mí la imagen del millor
no, then he started lying
no que Luego encima se puso a mentir
about his ban, no ban, and all that stuff,
sobre su baneo no baneo y todo el rollo
there he had his career hanging by a
ese ahí tuvo su carrera pendiente de un
thread, eh, I mean, his channel, his career, no,
hilo eh o sea su canal su carrera no
because maybe he would have gone to another
porque a lo mejor se hubiera ido a otra
platform, but the Twitch channel,
plataforma pero el canal de Twitch
look, they closed it for that reason, I
fíjate tú que te lo cierran por
think that in the end they didn't
eso que creo que al final no se lo
close it because, well, since he's a
cerraron porque bueno como es una
person with numbers and everything, some
persona con números y demás algún
contact would take it away from him, another different ex,
contacto le quitaría otro ex diferente
okay, for any other reason, but
vale por cualquier otro motivo pero
imagine if your ex reports you, what
imagínate que te denuncia tu ex que le
could he do?  I shouldn't have reported him
le podría no debería haberlo denunciado
the truth is you don't wish that on anyone but
la verdad no se lo desea a nadie pero
if you do
que si haces
that let's say the things he said about Cristinini
eso sea las cosas que dijo de cristinini
and the things that Cristinini said afterwards
y las cosas que contó cristinini después
well let's see I remember like oh what did he
bueno a ver me acuerdo como que ay qué
say that we said this kid he's
fue lo que dijo que dijimos este chaval
not very
no es muy
smart what did he say when
listo qué fue lo que dijo cuando
Cristinini exploded recently do you remember
cristinini estalló hace poco os acordáis
that Cristinini exploded recently and
que cristinini estalló hace poco y se
Cristinini started saying that he had
puso a decir cristinini que había
suffered
sufrido maltrato
psychological abuse and he said something like oh
psicológico y él dijo algo como que ay
what did he say that we said this
qué fue lo que dijo que dijimos este
guy Oh what is it F F what he said
chico Ay qué es lo que F F lo que dijo
but yes they are things that I say this
pero sí son cosas que que yo digo este
kid I mean how are you going to take a kid
chaval o sea cómo vas a [__] un chaval
that you may like you may dislike
que te puede caer bien te puede caer mal
with manche whatever you want it may
con manche lo que tú quieras te puede
seem stupid to you idiot But if it's
parecer tonto idiota Pero si te está
costing you if the kid is telling you
costando si te está contando El Chaval
in a video that he
en un vídeo
has I don't know how many
e que tiene no sé cuántos trastornos
mental disorders how are you going to start
mentales cómo te vas a poner a
telling him Ramón Today is the day that he is a
decirle Ramón Hoy es el día que es un
[ __ ] [ __ ] my boyfriend left me he told me
[__] [__] mi novio se fue me avisó
his family blamed me for not believing him he
su familia me culpó por no creerle
tried until he succeeded  what
intentó hasta que lo logró lo que dice
this character says is devastating but
este personaje resulta devastador pero
apart from that Of course you can try to commit
es que aparte Claro que puedes intentar
suicide and not
suicidarte y no
succeed in any of the ways
conseguirlo en cualquiera de las formas
that
que
exist in any of the ways like
existen en cualquiera de las formas en
taking a pill like hanging yourself like it ca
el de tomar pastilla en el de colgarte
n't fail Of course it can
en el de no puede fallar Claro que puede
fail or someone can suddenly intervene
fallar o que de repente intervenga
a thousand things
alguien mil cosas
if I try to suar I won't come to you
si yo me intento suar no os vendré
in a month saying chat I
dentro de un mes diciendo chat Me
tried to commit suicide no no no my father will post a
intenté suicidar no no no pondrá un
tweet and say Emilio r has
tweet mi padre y dirá Emilio r se han
Pull thrown himself out the window and not even that well
Pull estrado por la ventana y ni eso
probably He wouldn't jump out the
pues seguramente No saltaría por la
window you know but I don't know if that's his case
ventana sabes pero no sé si es su caso
obviously but for me people who have
obviamente pero a mí la gente
tried to commit suicide for me it's already a
de intentado suicidar para mí ya es una
great red flag I really believe it on
grandiosa red flag de verdad lo creo
top of that I know people who have
encima yo sé de gente que se ha
really tried to suar because they've been
intentado suar de verdad porque ha
admitted because such And you know
estado ingresado porque tal Y sabes
how many times have they said
cuántas veces han dicho alguna vez en
somewhere that they've tried to commit suicide
algún lado que se han intentado suicidar
none none none it's not talked about it's
ninguna ninguna ninguna no se habla es
taboo don't touch it's a [ __ ] coincidence
tabú no se toca da la [__] casualidad
that everyone who tries
que todo el mundo que se intenta su
wants the [ __ ] attention of saying that they've
quiere la [__] atención de decir que se
tried to
ha intentado
go there yes I can quite
idar ahí sí puedo estar bastante de
agree with him eh a little eh or  It's
acuerdo con él eh un poco eh o sea es
weird that you
rarete que lo
tell it, another thing is that if you
cuentes otra cosa es que que si lo
get it and if you do it, you start
consigues y si lo haces empieces
telling it, your
a lo cuente tu tu
people, but you
gente pero que tú mismo lo
tell it yourself, there, no longer by logic, eh, I
cuentes ahí ya no por lógica eh que me
can be wrong and I imagine that each
puedo equivocar y me imagino que cada
person will be a world
persona será un mundo
but
pero
For what
Con qué
reason don't you, I mean, why, why would
motivo no te o sea por qué por qué
n't it bother you,
motivo no te incomodaría
eh, to tell it And remember it No, why
eh contarlo Y recordarlo No por qué
make it public, what do you need to know
hacerlo público qué necesitas para sabes
what you need to make it
qué necesitas para hacerlo
public?
público
Yes, yes, but I understand that each person is
Sí sí pero entiendo que cada persona es
a world, eh, it will depend a lot on each case,
un mundo eh dependerá mucho de cada caso
each context, then on the
de cada contexto de luego en la
situation in which you tell it. No, how
situación en la que lo cuente No como lo
can you tell it, how can you tell it as
puedes contar como lo puedes contar como
a warning, how to make it visible, you can
un aviso como visibilizar lo puedes
tell it like? Hey, get out of there, I've been there
contar como Oye sal de ahí que yo he
and I've come
estado y he
out, people who claim that whoever does it
salido la gente que asegura que el que
doesn't warn, normally they haven't
lo hace no avisa normalmente no ha
had direct contact with a case,
tenido contacto directo con un caso la
people don't want to suffer. It's not that there
gente no quiere sufrir No es que también
are also cases of people who make it
hay casos de gente que que que se lo
up to get attention, there, this
inventa para llamar la atención hay esto
is like everything, I mean, there are a lot of
es como todo o sea hay mucha gente
liars and you
mentirosa y
know,
sabes
but it's not like, let's see, for
pero tampoco es como a ver a ver por
example,
ejemplo
eh, you can take it and you can say that it's
eh tú puedes [__] y puedes decir que de
normal  It strikes me that a
normal me llama la atención que una
person who just went through this
persona que acaba de pasar esto pues
makes a video. Well, I don't know what, well, it doesn't
haga un vídeo Pues no sé qué pues no me
add up to me. Because while you were
cuadra Porque mientras que tú estabas
doing this at the same time you were doing that
haciendo esto a la vez estabas haciendo
other thing, what can I say? Imagine that you
lo otro qué te digo yo imagínate que tú
got it around the time of Comanche,
coges por las fechas de Comanche dices
you say Comanche was laughing his ass off
tú Comanche se estaba partiendo la [__]
and I don't know something that doesn't
y Yo qué sé algo que no te
add up to you, I don't know what example to give so as not to
cuadre no sé qué ejemplo ponero para no
be unfortunate at this time, the
ser desafortunado en estos momentos la
truth is, but you can have an opinion. Well, I do
verdad pero tú puedes opinar Pues yo
n't believe this one because in
este no me lo creo porque dentro del
context there are strange things there are things that
contexto Hay cosas raras hay cosas que
aren't so strange, the report says this
no son tan raras en el parte pone esto
in the report, you know what I'm telling you, but
en el parte sabes lo que te digo pero
one thing is that and another thing is that you
una cosa es esa y otra cosa es que tú
impose and generalize, it's not normal, and you
impongas y generalices no normal y tú
say you're not telling it, it's a matter of knowledge.
digas no lo cuentas es un tema sabur
Well, let's see. There will be people. Or maybe you
Bueno a ver Habrá gente O a lo mejor
can even say that the majority of
incluso puedes decir la mayoría de la
people then don't talk about this in public
gente luego no hablan de esto en público
or in a YouTube video or whatever.
o en un vídeo de YouTube o lo que sea
No, I don't know if that's the case with Comanche, but it
no no sé si es el caso de Comanche pero
is, but you can't say that
es pero no puedes decir que todo el
everyone is like that. The first thing that comes to
mundo sea así lo primero que se me viene
mind is when in the first  20
la cabeza cuando en los primeros 20
second video says a month ago
segundos de vídeo dice hace un mes me
trying for me is already
intentar para mí ya es
[Music]
[Música]
like it could be the second case of that
como que puede ser el segundo caso del
you have less IQ than a potato
de que tienes menos iq que una patata
chip you know and you fail it could be it could be
frita sabes y fallas puede ser podría
that you really fail it's one of two or
ser que realmente falles es una de dos o
you're an attention keeper or you're very stupid there's no
eres una attention hor o eres muy tonto
more chill it's not serious it's
no hay más chill no va en serio va en
serious it's my opinion that today you go
serio es mi opinión que a día de hoy vas
anywhere and everyone comes at you
a cualquier lado y te viene todo el
let's
mundo se te abajo a
see It's that I've tried three times
ver Es que yo me intentado su tres veces
the girlfriend of the girlfriend of the What's his name of the
la novia de la novia del Cómo se llama
rich guy is that he has a history of
del riquito es que tiene historial de
four attempts I ate my balls ha
cuatro intentos me coma los huevos ha
attempts of what are you trying four
intentos de de qué te intentas cuatro
times are you so stupid to fail four
veces tan tonta eres para fallar cuatro
times in a row don't [ __ ] with me today it
veces seguidas no me jodas a día de hoy
's always the same maybe I'm wrong No no it's that
es siempre lo mismo quizá me equivoco No
you You don't know many
no es que que tú Tú no sabes muchas
times How are people Eh I mean many
veces Cómo está la gente Eh o sea muchas
times that
veces que
Eh many times you don't know how are
Eh muchas veces tú no sabes cómo está la
people there there are for example people that you
gente haí hay por ejemplo gente que tú
can withstand a certain downpour at
puedes aguantar cierto chaparrón en
any moment you're used to it and
cualquier momento estás acostumbrado y
your dick gets up and then there are people that
te suba la [__] y luego hay gente que
you maybe don't know how they're
tú a lo mejor no sabes cómo se está
taking it  that he's falling maybe I'm
tomando la que le esté cayendo quizá me
wrong about him I'm obviously giving
equivoque con él estoy obviamente dando
the benefit of the doubt I have to watch the
el beneficio de la duda he de verme el
video And such But when
vídeo Y tal Pero a mí cuando me viene
someone comes to me and tells me that this person
alguien me dic es que esta persona se
tried to commit suicide I already think in my head what an
intentó suicidar yo ya en mi cabeza
[ __ ] I always
pienso tremendo [__] siempre lo
think instantly maybe I'm
pienso instantáneamente quizás estoy
wrong 2014 I was diagnosed with
equivocado 2014 fui diagnosticado con
bipolar disorder and manic
trastorno bipolar y trastorno maníaco
depression I found one I do have an opinion yes
depresivo encontré una tengo opinón sí
about taking things for depression no
sobre tomar cosas para la depresión no
I want to get into that let's see if I have an
Quiero meterme en ese a ver sí tengo una
opinion But since it's from ignorance I'm
opinión Pero como es desde la ignorancia
not going to give it
no voy a darla
better I'm going to give this [ __ ] a hard time I do
mejor le voy a hacer un vieo a este
n't believe this is an
[__] No me creo que este sea un
influencer That's my Fran Do it Fran
influencer Ese es mi Fran Hazlo Fran
but you're going to do it now or you're going to
pero lo vas a hacer ya o que lo vas a
do it calmly when you think
hacer tranquilamente cuando pienses
well good thing he didn't say anything or
bien menos mal que no ha dicho nada o
rather good thing he didn't say what he was
sea menos mal que no ha dicho lo que
thinking
está lo que ha pensado
here but dude can you talk to me on
aquí pero cabrón me puedes hablar por el
WhatsApp You don't have to spend money I've
WhatsApp No te tienes que gastar dinero
told you a thousand times dude but you're
te lo he dicho ya mil veces cabrón pero
going to do it now or rather to wait for him to
lo vas a hacer ya o o sea para esperarlo
laugh here at the four
para para reírnos aquí de las cuatro
things he's going to say or rather less  bad
cosas que le va a decir o sea menos mal
that he didn't say Good thing he didn't
que no ha dicho Menos mal que no ha
say what he was thinking at this
dicho lo que estaba pensando en este
moment when he said I'm going to keep quiet
momento cuando ha dicho me voy a callar
about what I think about people who take
lo lo que pienso sobre la gente que toma
medication let's
medicación
see people take medication for
a ver la gente Toma medicación por la
Mental Health too of course but of course but of course
Salud Mental también
Mental Health
claro pero claro que la la Salud Mental
Of course they take
Claro que se
medication [ __ ] Well, I don't know, I do
medica [__] Pues anda que no conozco yo
n't know friends who
anda que no conozco yo amigos que que
need medication to feel
necesitan la medicación para encontrarse
good in a good mood to be well for, I mean,
bien de ánimos para estar bien para o
that's why he has his medication
sea eso tiene su medicación
too, come on, this guy thinks that the one who
también vamos este se cree que el que
studies psychiatry is a random one, not
estudia psiquiatría es pu al azar no
like the one who's playing, not to get
como el que está jugando no para ponerse
a leg up, my goodness
una pata madre mía
uncle Fran this is your thing eh destroy it
tío Fran esto es cosa tuya eh destrúyelo
suki a
suki un
kiss it's that this kid has negative IQ, I do
beso es que es iq en negativo este
n't want to disrespect him, I know
chaval no quiero faltarle al respeto yo
that he disrespects me eh I mean, I know that
sé que él me lo falta eh o sea yo sé que
he insults me whenever he feels like it
él me insulta cada vez que le da la gana
and everything but I'm not him, I mean but the thing is that
y todo pero yo no soy él o sea pero es
this guy has negative IQ
que este tío es iq en negativo
eh you
eh
don't play with Mental Health let's see
con la Salud Mental no se juega a ver
Anica you can question and I think we have
Anica tú puedes cuestionar y creo que lo
done it on many occasions when there
hemos hecho en muchas ocasiones cuando
are cases that you don't  they fit of someone
hay casos que no te cuadran de alguien
who is pulling their nose or who is
que se está tirando el moco o que está
using or who is using
utilizando o que está utilizando los
mental problems and Mental Health
problemas mentales y la Salud Mental
as an excuse for their lies like for
como excusa para sus mentiras como por
example Lali no that she has invented a
ejemplo Lali no que se ha inventado una
rape she has invented I don't know what she
violación se ha inventado no sé qué se
has invented I don't know how much so there you
ha inventado no sé cuánto entonces tú
question but here she is generalizing
cuestionas pero aquí está generalizando
one is that she is saying nonsense anyway
una es que está diciendo tontería sea es
this kid is what I tell you I mean I
que este chaval es lo que os digo o sea
believed that this kid was not he was not
yo yo me creía que este chaval no era no
stupid I believed that it was a role
era tonto yo me creía que era un papel
that he plays to exploit his character
que él hace para explotar su personaje
but of course I see things man a
pero claro yo es que ya veo cosas tío un
guy who lives in Andorra and who has to
tío que vive en andorra y que tiene que
behave in Andorra because he is
portarse bien en andorra porque está
there paying taxes to pay a
allí pagando los impuestos para pagar un
10 instead of a
10 en vez de un
53 and the guy starts insulting the
53 y el tío se pone a insultar a la
police what t is that he is
policía qué t es que s
stupid Look, I was walking through the
tonto Mira está estaba caminando por el
sanctuary that I am listening to you with the
santuario que te voy escuchando con Los
helmets and I don't believe Look, I was
cascos y no me creo Mira estaba
walking through the sanctuary that I am
caminando por el santuario que te voy
listening to you with the helmets and I don't believe
escuchando con Los cascos y no me creo
what I just heard I do
lo que lo que acabo de escuchar Es que
n't believe it I mean I have to
no me lo creo O sea me he tengo que
go here in the office  to see
meter aquí en la ofi para ver la cara de
this guy's face because I'm freaking out, I mean,
este tío porque estoy flipando o sea
these are no longer kids this is a
estos ya no son niñatos esto es un
monster, I mean, uh, what you can't do
engendro o sea eh lo que no se puede
is release this message
hacer es soltar este mensaje
because this guy, I don't know what he's
porque es que este tío yo no sé qué ha
been through in his life if he's ever left
vivido en su vida si ha salido alguna
his room or done anything more
vez de su habitación o ha hecho algo más
than say
que decir
stupid things but damn, throughout his
tonterías pero [__] a lo largo de su
life he's going to lose friends he's going to lose
vida va a perder amigos va a perder
family he's going to lose people because they commit
familiares va a perder gente porque se
suicide, of course,
suicidan claro
uh, and of course people don't commit suicide right away
eh Y claro que la gente no se suicida de
there are many who do but there are many
una hay muchos que sí pero hay muchos
who after three or four attempts
que después de tres o cuatro intentos se
end up committing suicide, I mean, what
termina suicidando o sea lo que ha dicho
this guy really said, uh, he's talking about
este tío de verdad eh está hablando de
IQ, he's talking about an idiot, he's talking about, I'm
iq está hablando de tonto está hablando
going to make a short video, but
de le voy a hacer un vídeo cortito pero
of course what you can't do
desde luego que lo que no se puede hacer
is release that and say that you're an
es soltar eso y decir que eres
influencer, I mean, this guy,
influencer o sea este tío
uh, well, I'm going to shut up, I'm going to shut up,
eh Bueno me voy a callar me voy a callar
no, don't shut up, don't
no no te calles no te
shut up, but I'm going to say several things, what
calles pero voy a decir varias cosas lo
suicide is, what it's like to live it in
que es el suicidio lo que es vivirlo en
your own, in your own family, this guy
tu propia en tu propia familia este tío
is a, well, I'll make a video,
es un Eh bueno haré un vídeo
yeah, but don't shut up, don't  cuts but if
s Sí pero no te calles no te cortes pero
this kid is not normal but
si es que este chaval no es normal pero
if this kid is not normal This kid
si este chaval no es normal Este chaval
has a
tiene el iq en
negative IQ, I mean he has a negative IQ
negativo o sea tiene el iq en negativo
how are you going to say that it's a flash network
tú cómo vas a decir que es una red flash
when a person tells you that they have
cuando una persona te dice que se ha
attempted suicide let's see or that they
intentado suicidar vamos a ver o que se
have attempted or that they have
ha intentado o que tiene problemas
mental problems let's see each case is a
mentales vamos a ver cada caso es un
world of course there are cases that
mundo por supuesto que hay casos que
we question But if here we have
cuestionamos Pero si aquí lo habremos
done it a thousand
hecho mil
times how not but man I think that I think that there are
veces cómo no pero hombre Yo creo que yo
some cases where you have
creo que hay algunos casos que tienes
doubts there are some cases that are eh with
dudas hay algunos casos que son eh con
neons careful false cases you
neones cuidadito casos falsos me
understand and even so you have to treat it I mean
entiendes y aún así tienes que tratarlo
remember how I treated the
o sea acordaros de cómo traté yo lo del
Ali thing at the beginning do you remember do you remember
Ali al principio os acordáis os acordáis
how I treated the Ali thing at the beginning
de cómo traté yo lo del Ali al principio
at the beginning I
al principio
said prudence caution I don't believe it I think she
decía prudencia cautela no me la creo
's lying but I'm going to
Creo que está mintiendo pero me voy a
feel really bad If all of a sudden this girl
sentir muy mal Si de repente esta chica
is telling the truth and the side be
está diciendo la verdad y laio lado
careful I don't know what I don't know how much you know
cuidado no sé qué no sé cuánto sabes
but you how are you going to say that it's already a
pero tú cómo vas a decir que ya es una
refl that someone tells you let's
refl que alguien te diga vamos a
see when on the
ver cuando al
contrary to me when they have  warned Hey, do
contrario a mí cuando me han avisado Oye
n't give this guy too much trouble, he's seeing a
este chico no le den mucha caña que está
psychologist, they've told me, and be careful
de psicólogo me han dicho y ten cuidado
because maybe he'll be with you, well, I try to avoid
que a lo mejor pues yo Procuro esquivar
the topics of one of the ot, I mean, when a
los temas de uno del ot o sea cuando una
person is telling you, or a
persona te está diciendo ya que o un
friend has passed it to me, no, a friend has passed it to me
amigo me ha pasado no un amigo me ha
that they have been telling me that
pasado que me ha estado comentando que
we are screwed and that he is out of
estamos jodidos y que se queda sin
work and that no job is working for him and that he
trabajo y que ningún trabajo le cuaja y
is taking medication and I don't know
que está tomando medicación y que no sé
what and that he has a Mental Health issue,
qué y que está con tema de Salud Mental
Lorena and I have been on the lookout,
hemos estado Lorena y yo pendiente
calling every day and such. Hey,
llamando todos los días y tal Oye
discreetly, I don't feel like that either,
disimuladamente que tampoco se sient tal
but you worry because you don't know, you don't
pero te preocupas porque tú no sabes tú
know, let's see, I've heard stories, I've heard
sabes a ver yo he conocido historias yo
stories of people who
he conocido historias de gente que de
suddenly didn't say anything to anyone about how they
repente no le decía nada a nadie de cómo
were and you thought they were okay and they
estaba y te creías que estaba bien y no
weren't okay and it was too late,
estaba bien y era demasiado tarde
then when a person
después entonces cuando una persona te
gives you a
pega un
warning, the normal thing that you think is not that they are
aviso lo normal que tú piensas no es que
[ __ ] and that they are a
es un [__] y que es un [__]
[ __ ] [ __ ] now something else is what I
subnormal ahora otra cosa es lo que os
'm telling you something else is that there are
estoy diciendo otra cosa es que haya
signs and indications that
señales e indicios de que se está
Mental Health is being made fun of and it is
pitorreo de la Salud Mental y se está
joking around and what and that what you're saying is false
cachondeando y que y que sea falso lo
but for you to say no, they come to me
que contando pero que tú digas no a mí
first and tell me how are you
de primera me vienen y me dicen que tal
then Frank goes up he's going to be
Entonces yo me Frank sube estará
recording a video Alba is going to be recording
grabando un vídeo Alba estará grabando
a video While we're watching this he's
un vídeo Mientras que vemos esto
probably
seguramente a
crazy If I'm not telling you that you can't question Of course you can question
challado Si yo no te digo que no puedas
Of course you can with Of course you
cuestionar Claro que puedes con Claro
can question but if it's that
que puedes cuestionar pero si es que
here we've probably questioned surely 1
aquí hemos cuestionado seguramente 1
cases of people and maybe you can
casos de gente y a lo mejor puedes
question someone who really then is
cuestionar a alguien que realmente luego
really wrong and damn you've screwed
sí que está mal de verdad y [__] la
up
has cagado
no but each case is different within
no pero cada caso es diferente dentro de
its context within the whole story
su contexto dentro de toda la historia
but already in itself no then you can
pero ya de por si no luego tú puedes
say that normally people who have gone through
decir de normal la gente que ha pasado
this don't want to bring up the subject they don't
por esto no quieren sacar el tema no
want to talk about it normally no no they don't
quieren hablar del tema normalmente no
come out and tell it in a video
no no salen y lo cuentan en un vídeo
YouTube Okay but but don't make it
YouTube Bueno pero pero no ponerlo como
a rule 100% that is fulfilled the
una norma al 100% que se cumple decisión
most important decision of my life has been carried out by only one
más importante de mi vida lleva una sola
person
persona
000 I think it's the ridiculous prize until
000 creo que es el premio ridículo hasta
another complete video fell Why don't you
que cayó otro complet vídeo Por qué no
make a video talking to the camera What is
hace un vídeo hablando a cámara Qué es
this nonsense What is this [ __ ] is that there are
esta tontería Qué es esta [__] es que
people who are simply not worth it
hay gente simplemente que no vale para
social networks I think you have to
las redes sociales yo creo que se ha de
have a minimum of vision you have to
tener un mínimo de visión has de
understand that if you talk about a
entender que si hablas de un tema de
serious subject putting a disclaimer and doing a
serio poner un disclaimer y hacer una
[ __ ] Random like that is not going to save you talk about the
[__] Random así no te va a salvar habla
serious subject stand in front of the
del tema serio ponte delante de la
camera and talk for now what did
cámara y habla durante ahora que ha
random say I just remembered that
dicho random me acabo de acordar que
this guy defends the ccu and to
este defiende al ccu y por llevarle la
contradict him or rather he was killing himself with
contraria o sea se llevaba a matar con
the ccu this kid is not smart this kid
el ccu este chico no es listo este chico
is like that Really this kid is like that he had
es así De verdad este chico es que es
a stroke of luck with
así le ha venido un golpe de suerte con
that video game that he plays and he has won
el videojuego ese que él juega y ha Gan
a lot of money and but this kid no this
mucho dinero y pero este chico no este
kid no he is not smart for anything I just
chico no no es listo para Nada me acabo
remembered that he was killing himself with the
de acordar que se llevaba matar con el
cosu he has been killing himself all his life
coscu se ha llevado a matar toda la vida
with the ccu and when suddenly it
con el ccu y cuando de repente
comes out it goes viral because of the
sale se hace viral por el tema de la
evening thing about the cocu issue The guy has
velada lo del tema de cocu El tío lo ha
been defending him because it was Dallas who was the one who was the one who was
estado defendiendo porque era Dallas el
commenting on it like like
lo el que lo comenta como como el
turboplus there taking a picture with the cosu
turboplus allí hacerse foto con el cosu
at the evening because because well And he
en la velada porque porque bueno Y
also said it eh the enemy of my
además lo dijo eh el enemigo de mi
enemy is my
enemigo es mi
friend and she's a random  Ada what
amigo y es una randon Ada lo que ha
coscu has done there is nothing wrong with this
hecho coscu no tiene nada de malo
kid half an hour do that That's [ __ ]
chaval media hora haz eso That's fucking
it this is [ __ ] Random I went
it esto es una [__] Random me volví
completely crazy It's that I think there
completamente loco Es que creo que no
was not a time that we have said that
había una vez que hayamos dicho que
based the million No in this he is
basado el millón No en esto tiene la
right there was once when he was based and he
razón hubo una vez que estuvo basado y
got scared and went with
se acojonado y fue con el
chocas It was only one time that he was
chocas Solo fue una vez la que estuvo
based that he told chocas four
basado que le dijo al chocas cuatro
things that the million was right and
cosas que tenía la razón el millor y
then chocas got all like pi pi p
luego el choca se le puso así pi pi p
come on I'm going to debate and [ __ ] off
venga subo a debatir y se cojon
no Javi misha said that the kid who
no Javi misha ha dicho que el chaval que
disappeared is having a
ha desaparecido se está pegando una
good party and that he is seeing how his
fiesta buena y que está viendo cómo le
Followers are increasing
Seguidores madre
my goodness that's what he
mía eso ha
said but
dicho pero
[ __ ] How little tact don't you have to have a
[__] Qué poco tacto no hay que tener un
little more respect than that kid the
poco más de respeto que ese chaval la
story looks really
historia pinta muy
bad I am about to take this case to several
mal estoy por llevar este caso a varias
associations says
asociaciones dice
Virginia is that whoever has had a
Virginia es que el que haya tenido una
story
historia
close whoever has had a story
cerca el que haya tenido una historia
close will be seeing the blood
cerca le estará ir viendo la sangre
heard this guy
escuchado este tío
eh Let's see I think there is click I think there is
eh A ver creo que hay click creo que hay
clim more summarized without having to swallow
clim má resumido sin tener que tragarme
toner it
tonero
is not  also a big piece of elor
no es además un pedazo grande de elor
besides being one of the stupidest
además de ser una personas más estúpidas
and most self-centered people in T is also a
y egocéntricas de T es además un pedazo
big piece of impes And if you still don't understand
grande de impes Y si aún no entiendes el
why I say this it's for this very reason if
Por qué digo esto es por esto mismo si
you try to commit suicide and fail you're not
te intentas suicidar y fallas no eres
very intelligent or you're looking for attention I have
muy inteligente o buscas atención tengo
my opinion on it How the [ __ ] can you
mi opinión sobre ello Cómo [__] puedes
say that if someone tries to commit
decir que si es que alguien se intenta
suicide they're not intelligent stupid is
suicidar no es inteligente tontas son
the [ __ ] you talk on the
las [__] que hablas por
internet it's really exaggerated I
internet es que es muy exagerado
ask eh I
pregunto eh
ask Hey they've closed my
pregunto Oye me han cerrado en
live on Twitch they've closed my
Twitch el directo me han cerrado el
live on
directo en
Twitch Why
Twitch Por qué
bro Ah no no no
bro Ah no no no
what do you think is too exaggerated to believe
que pensáis que es muy exagerado creer
What's wrong with the volume I have it turned up
Qué le pasa el volumen Lo tengo subido
now it's fine do you think it's too
ahora está bien creéis que es muy
exaggerated to think that they should put
exagerado pensar que le deberían poner
[Music]
[Música]
a little tap for what he
un un toquecito por eso que ha
said I'm not saying a ban or anything like that
dicho no te digo un baneo ni nada por el
but a
estilo pero un
little tap hasn't
toquecito no se ha
slipped in and then you call yourself
colado además de luego tirarte de
egocentric saying that it's a problem
egocéntrico diciendo que es un problema
since he himself recognizes that he has
puesto que él mismo reconoce que tiene
an ego problem since he was a kid but
un problema con el ego desde chico pero
to this day he's not even
hasta el día de hoy ni siquiera le
interested in solving that by giving
interesa solucionar eso dándole [__]
literally free [ __ ] to people like
literalmente gratuita a gente como a
carch And if you are a follower of his the truth
carch Y si eres seguidor de él la verdad
is that you also give me [ __ ] pity because
es que me das también [__] lástima puo
since he is a public figure you are
es que como es una figura pública
probably followers too and those
probablemente suores también y aquellos
who continue following him probably
que lo continúan siguiendo probablemente
share perhaps the same idea or come
compartan quizás la misma idea o lleguen
to share that idea and the thing is that I do
a compartir esa idea y es que al millor
not give any harm to the fellow in fact I hope that
no le deo ningún mal de hecho espero que
one day he sees these videos again and
algún día vea estos videos de nuevo y
really thinks about the amount of [ __ ] he
realmente piens la cantidad de [__]
said and well What do you think, the
que dijo y bueno Qué opinan el
fellow? Let's see
millor a ver voy a ver
what level of ignorance and lack of
si qué nivel de ignorancia y falta de
empathy that the fellow has on top of him, he is a
empatía que lleva el millor encima es un
piece of garbage of a character and I still do not
pedazo de basura de personaje y aún no
understand how he has real followers
entiendo cómo tiene seguidores posta
I hope he never goes through the suffering
Ojalá que nunca pase por el sufrimiento
Oh I maintain the everyone there is no exception if
Oh mantengo el todos no hay excepción si
you try to commit suicide and fail you are not
te intentas suicidar y fallas no eres
very intelligent it may be that you do
muy inteligente puede puede ser que sí
have suicidal intentions but you
que tengas intenciones suicidas pero no
are not very
eres muy
intelligent Oh you seek attention I mean I
inteligente Oh buscas atención es decir
maintain the I maintain my opinion on
mantengo el mantengo mi opinión sobre
it
ello chico
silly boy if you try to fail you are not very
tonto si te intentas fallas no eres muy
intelligent it may be that you do have
inteligente puede ser que sí que tengas
intentions but it is not very intelligent or you
intenciones pero no es muy inteligente o
seek attention I maintain my opinion
buscas atención mantengo mi opinión
on it Oh my God it is true Oh My
sobre ello Oh my God es cierto Oh My
[ __ ] God it is  true there is no
Fucking God es cierto no hay discusión
possible discussion if you try you fail you're stupid it is
posible te intentas fallas eres tonto es
what it is you are either a [ __ ] idiot or
lo que hay eres tonto de [__] o
you have very bad luck but again it
tienes muy mala suerte pero de nuevo pu
would be a very very very very very
sería un porcentaje muy muy muy muy muy
small percentage or you are a tension hour it is one of
pequeño o eres una tension hor es una de
two that is to say it is either one or the other there is no
dos es decir es o una o la otra no hay
third scale I don't [ __ ] know
un tercer baremo I don't fucking know de
again everything said in this Stream is
nuevo todo lo dicho en este Stream es
tumor and it is satire if someone has
tumor y es sátira si alguien le ha
offended Twitch do not ban me please this is
ofendido Twitch no me banes por favor es
where I wanted to
donde Quería
get to now then he has realized
llegar ahora luego se ha dado cuenta de
the barbarity
la barbaridad
of this subject obviously I am not saying that it
no de este tema obviamente no digo que
is the case of Comanche but I believe that
sea el caso de Comanche pero yo creo que
if you try there are two possibilities either you are
si intentas hay dos posibilidades o eres
completely mentally [ __ ] or you
completamente put [__] mental o
are looking for attention there are no
buscas atención no hay intentos de
suicide attempts unless you are super bad I
suicidio a no ser que seas super mal
tried to commit suicide I will not come to you in
intento suicidar no os vendré dentro de
a month saying chat I tried to commit suicide
un mes diciendo chat Me intenté suicidar
no no no no my father will put a tweet and
no no no no pondrá un tweet mi padre y
say Emilio r has Pulled himself out the
dirá Emilio r se han Pull estrado por la
window or not even that but surely He would not
ventana o y ni eso pero seguramente No
jump out the window you know but I do not know
saltaría por la ventana sabes pero no sé
if it is his case obviously but for me the
si es su caso obviamente pero a mí la
people of I have tried Look you are
gente de me he intentado Mira estáis
putting the chat  shelos 2.0 no no
poniendo el chat shelos 2.0 no no
literally has the same the same
literalmente tiene la misma la misma
capacity
capacidad
eh has the same capacity as the
eh tiene la misma capacidad que el el
zeal guy I mean you can put this guy I
celo tío O sea tú este tío lo puedes
mean I don't see him as
poner o sea yo yo es que no lo veo para
having the power that he
que este tío sea tenga el poder que que
has on the internet I mean I see him as a I mean
tenga en internet o sea yo lo veo para
the way he has of
un O sea la manera que tiene de
expressing himself the things that he says I see him
expresarse las cosas que dice yo lo veo
as one of these like the ones that
como un de estos como los que llevaba el
Carden wore Martian Chronicles to
carden crónicas marcianas para para
bring him in to say four stupid things
traerlo a que diga cuatro burradas
Knowing the context not that we shouldn't
Sabiendo el contexto no de que no hay
take him seriously and because like
que tomarlo en serio y porque como
when we bring
cuando traemos al
Marius but this guy has a
marius pero es que este chico tiene un
lot of followers
montón de seguidores
for me he's a great red flag I
para mí es una grandiosa red flag de
really believe it on top of that I know people who have
verdad lo creo encima yo sé de gente que
really tried because they've been
se ha intentado de verdad porque ha
admitted because such And you know
estado ingresado porque tal Y sabes
how many times have they said
cuántas veces han dicho alguna vez en
somewhere that they've tried to commit suicide
algún lado que se han intentado suicidar
none none none it's not talked about it's
ninguna ninguna ninguna no se habla es
taboo it's probably just a desire to screw Dallas
tabú no s serán ganas de [__] a Dallas
for his attempt I can't believe that
por su intento no me puedo creer que
someone says this for me it's the most
alguien diga esto para mí es de lo más
serious and painful thing this is coming out
grave y doloroso esto le está saliendo
of his soul eh I mean I think he doesn't
del alma eh o sea yo creo que esto no lo
have this  reconsidered what he said I mean he's
tiene recapacitado lo que ha dicho O sea
not even processing it at the
no lo está ni procesando en en el
moment he's saying what he thinks it's your
momento está diciendo lo que piensa te
turn it's a [ __ ] coincidence that
toca da la [__] casualidad que todo el
everyone who tries to commit suicide has the
mundo que se intenta suicidar tiere la
[ __ ] attention to say that they've
[__] atención de decir que se ha
tried to commit suicide I don't know if it's the
intentado suicidar no s no sé si es el
case with Comanche but it's the first thing that
caso de Comanche pero es lo primero que
comes to my mind when in the
se me viene la cabeza cuando en los
first 20 seconds of the video he says
primeros 20 segundos de vídeo dice hace
a month ago I tried to for me it's
un mes me intentar para mí ya es
[Music]
[Música]
like it could be the second case of you
como que puede ser el segundo caso del
have less IQ than a potato
de que tienes menos iq que una patata
chip you know and you fail it could be it could be that you
frita sabes y fallas puede ser podría
really fail it's one of two either you
ser que realmente falles es una de dos o
're an attention hog or you're really dumb it's not
eres un atention hor o eres muy tonto no
serious it's serious it's my opinion
va en serio va en serio es mi opinión
that these days you go anywhere and
que a día de hoy vas a cualquier lado y
you're all like Yeah it's that I've
te viene todo el en plan Sí es que yo he
tried three times the girlfriend of the
he intentado tres veces la novia de la
girlfriend of the What's her name of the rqu is that she
novia del Cómo se llama del rqu es que
has a history of four attempts I ate my
tiene historial de cuatro intentos me
balls attempts that you
coma los huevos intentos de que te
try four times how stupid are you to
intentas cuatro veces t tonta eres para
fail four times in a row it's always
fallar cuatro veces seguidas es siempre
the same maybe I'm wrong No no it's that
lo mismo quizá me equivoco No no es que
maybe I'm wrong  with him I'm
quizá me equivoque con él estoy
obviously giving the benefit of the doubt I have to
obviamente dando el beneficio de la duda
watch the video and all But
he de verme el vídeo Y tal Pero a mí
when someone comes to me and tells me that
cuando me viene alguien y me dice es que
this person tried to commit suicide I already
esta persona se intento sucidar yo ya en
think in my head what a [ __ ] [ __ ] I
mi cabeza pienso tremendo [__]
'm wrong the million I wanted And
estoy equivocado el millón quería Y por
why did he make this [ __ ] shitty video
qué ha hecho esta [__] [__] de vídeo
Why don't you make a video talking here I mean
Por qué no hace un vídeo hablando acá o
when someone comes to him saying
sea que cuando le viene alguien diciendo
this person tried to commit suicide he says what a
esta persona se intentó suicidar le dice
[ __ ] [ __ ] camera What is this
tremendo [__] cámara Qué es esta
nonsense What is this [ __ ] there are
tontería Qué es esta [__] es que hay
people who are simply not good at
gente simplemente que no vale para las
social networks I think you have to
redes sociales yo creo que se ha de
have a minimum of vision you have to
tener un mínimo de visión has de
understand that if you talk about a
entender que si hablas de un tema de
serious subject putting a disclaimer and doing a
serio poner un disclaimer y hacer una
[ __ ] random like that is not going to save you
[__] Random de así no te va a salvar
talk about the serious subject stand in front of the
habla del tema serio ponte delante la
camera and talk for half an hour do that That's What
cámara y habla durante media hora haz
this is a [ __ ] ripped
eso That's What esto es una [__] romada
victimhood I don't know everyone is kind of
victimismo no sé todo el mundo es medio
cool these days practically Hello
rado a día de hoy prácticamente Hola
Twitter Well I'm very skeptical about
Twitter Bueno yo soy muy escéptico con
these things to me honestly maybe I'm an
estas cosas a mí de verdad quizás soy un
[ __ ] maybe I'm ignorant
[__] quizás un ignorante puede ser
but when someone comes to me and I'm
pero a mí cuando me viene alguien y me
skeptical
escéptico
tent that no my goodness that's not
tent eso no madre mía es que eso no es
even being skeptical let's see You
ni siquiera ser escéptico a ver Tú
can be skeptical about many things eh
puedes ser escéptico con muchas cosas eh
You have to take things in fact in
Tú tienes que tomarte las de hecho de
fact here we always take things
hecho siempre aquí nos tomamos las cosas
with skepticism always always you have to
con escepticismo siempre siempre hay que
be skeptical always with everything goes
ser escéptico siempre con todo vale Por
Why well let's see but you always support the
qué bueno a ver pero siempre apoyas a
people who are victims you always
las personas que son víctimas siempre
support the victims let's see one
apoyas a los víctimas vamos a ver una
thing is that you
cosa es que tú
H we're always going to see there are people who
H siempre te vamos a ver hay gente que
confuse being skeptical with
confunde el ser escéptico con
eh with always having to
eh con que siempre te tienes que
position yourself against the victims that
posicionar en contra de las víctimas que
when someone comes out telling something that you
cuando sale alguien contando algo que tú
never have to believe because
nunca lo tienes que creer porque siempre
the girls always lie they make up I don't know what we're
las tías mienten se inventan no sé qué
not going to see it depends on the whole context it
no vamos a ver depende todo el contexto
depends on what you hear But of
depende de lo que tú escuches Pero por
course you're not going to believe
supuesto tú no te vas a creer un
mistreatment, abuse, I don't know what
maltrato un abuso un no sé qué
simply because of one person's word you
simplemente por la palabra de una
understand me you have to
persona me entiendes tú tienes que
listen to things and so on and I understand
escuchar las cosas y demás y entiendo
that there are times that it creates
que haya veces que te crea una
distrust but what
desconfianza pero es que lo que está
this guy is saying is what this guy is
diciendo este tío es lo que está
saying that any person
diciendo este tío que cualquier persona
and who says that has  tried to commit suicide
e que diga que se ha intentado suicidar
is a lie it's to attract attention and
es mentira que para llama la atención y
people who really have
que las personas que realmente tengan
mental problems shouldn't talk about it
problemas mentales que no lo deben de
because it's a taboo subject,
decir que es un tema
stupid, I mean, I think that you're not going
tonto o sea es que yo creo que que no te
to call yourself the dumbest person on the internet
V a decir el más tonto de internet
Because Turbo plan exists but it's
Porque existe Turbo plan pero es que es
fabric eh I mean it's
tela eh o sea es que es
brutal and when someone comes to me and
brutal y cuando me viene alguien y me
says I tried to commit suicide I think what an
dice me he intentado suicidar pienso lo
idiot you are Maybe it's
que eres ser [__] Quizás es culpa
my fault okay I don't [ __ ] know
mía puede ser vale I don't fucking know
maybe it's my thing well that's the
puede ser que sea cosa mía pu es lo
first thing that comes to my head when they
primero que me viene la cabeza cuando me
tell me that what will the psychologist think of that
dic eso qué pensara la psicóloga de ese
video you're giving me cancer it could be it could be
vídeo me das cáncer puede ser puede ser
but it is what but it's what always comes to my
pero es lo que pero es lo que me viene a
head
la cabeza siempre
buah buah man
buah buah tío
ah
ah
my god my god how cool my god how cool
madre mía madre mía qué
man Ha one
pasada madre mía qué pasada tío Ja una
thing is skepticism and another is insulting and
cosa es escepticismo y otra insultar y
saying that you shouldn't take anything for
decir que no hay que tomar nada para la
depression totally No no it's that
depresión totalmente No no es que está
someone is throwing there it's that they are talking
lanzando ahí uno es que está hablando
nonsense
burradas
you can talk about you can talk about
tú puedes hablar de tú puedes hablar de
nonsense and nonsense about other topics
barbaridades y burradas de otros temas
but I believe that there are topics that should be respected, I  I
pero yo creo que hay temas que hay que
think there are topics that should be
yo creo que hay temas que hay que
respected
respetar a no ser a no
unless the topic has already been denied that it
ser que ya el tema esté desmentido que
is a person you
sea una persona
know what, dude shut up when you
sabes [__] tío Cállate que cuando te
refer to Misha you mean this guy who
refieres a misha te refieres a este tío
likes the one who says that
al que le gustan al que dice que las
girls the one who says that girls are
niñas al que dice que las niñas están
very developed at 11 years old not that
muy desarrolladas con 11 años no que las
11 year old girls are already very
niñas de 11 años ya están muy
developed dude I don't know why when you
desarrolladas tío no sé por qué cuando
told me
me habéis dicho
Misha the thought came to mind this
misha se me ha venido a la cabeza El
strong kid who hangs out with
chaval este fuertote que se junta con el
Nilo it will be very likely that he got injured at the
Nilo dará mucho que se lesionó en la
party
velada
Oh if this guy says so I expect it of
Ah si lo dice este tío me lo espero
course I didn't expect it from the other
claro no me lo esperaba del otro
guy what's the other guy's name,
muchacho Cómo se llama el otro
so hard we're going to hit you he does
muchacho así fuerte te vamos te pega una
n't give you a scare like that and he takes you
[__] no te pega un susto así y y te
down his name is similar too he was also
desmonta se llama parecido también se
called similar too miso well
llamaba parecido también miso pues
when you told me I thought it
cuando me lo habéis dicho me creía que
was that guy and I said damn what a
era ese muchacho y he dicho [__] qué
load of rubbish he said but if this is the one who
barbaridad eso ha dicho pero si es este
told him about this yeah I
el que le ha dicho de este sí me lo
expect it Misha thinks the
espero misha piensa que el chaval
missing kid from Córdoba is having
desaparecido de Córdoba se está montando
the best party  of his life my goodness
la mejor fiesta de su vida madre mía
this is tremendous man I mean this is
esto es tremendo tío o sea esto es
tremendous for those who don't know what's going on
tremendo para el que no sepa Qué es lo
in Córdoba, the Boy from Córdoba
de Córdoba lo del Muchacho de Córdoba
today Precisely on telesalseo
hoy Precisamente en telesalseo
the first hour of the live broadcast on that
la primera hora del directo sobre ese
subject why
tema por qué
because come on in fact I've been I do
porque vamos de hecho es que he estado
n't know if it was seen very well to see
no sé si se habrá visto muy bien a ver
but I've been at the top of the news
pero he estado al pie de la noticia
because the police were searching with
porque estaba la policía buscando con
the dogs
los perros
precisely and come on in fact when I
precisamente y vamos de hecho yo cuando
was there I say wow
estaba allí digo fuf
Here here it is look
Aquí aquí
you look at it another way
mira tú míralo de otra forma zona de
tired area Sia later we're going to put
cansas Sia después vamos a poner
images look here you come back Ai yes I don't know and I already have the
imágenes mira aquí vuelves Ai si noigo y
same as I was
tengo ya igual que iba
cho back to configure cameras
cho vuelta laa de configurar cámaras
after okay Yes yes it has been seen it ca
tras vale Sí sí se ha
n't be seen look look
visto no se ve mira
Yes yes Well but that seems to be an
mira Sí sí Bueno pero eso pare ser una
ambulance that seems to be an ambulance no
ambulancia eso par ser una ambulancia no
but but In what area are they there there in the
pero pero En qué zona están allí allí al
background are Javi there in the background look look it's that you
fondo están Javi allí al fondo mira mira
can't see it because the
es que no lo podéis ver porque la
quality doesn't allow it okay of course H Well you can almost
calidad no lo da vale claro H Pues casi
see eh No it can't be seen it can't be seen that's it It's that no I have
se ve eh No no se ve no se ve eso es Es
n't been able to prepare the
que no no he podido preparar bien el
live broadcast well because we had
directo porque nosotros teníamos
prepared eh I spent a live broadcast the two of us
preparad eh pasé un directo los dos
talking about the subject  Hey
hablando del tema
look here are the cars and a
eh mira aquí están los coches y una
police van behind eh we
furgoneta policial detrás eh nosotros
have prepared the live in another
tenemos preparados el directo de otra
way to talk about the subject we
forma para para hablar del tema nosotros
from the studio Okay and we had videos
desde el estudio Vale y teníamos vídeos
prepared and things prepared and
preparados y cosas preparadas y de
suddenly well it happened That's good that
repente pues ha terado que Que bueno que
the police
la policía de
suddenly went to the neighborhood to the last place
repente ha ido al barrio al último sitio
where the boy had been seen with
donde se había visto al muchacho con
dogs and such and it looked like they were going to
perros y demás y tenía toda la pinta de
find something the truth is there
que iban a encontrar algo la verdad Allí
things were being talked about and such And I went
se estaban hablando cosas y tal Y he ido
running he was there at the bottom of
corriendo estaba estaba allí al pie de
the news and and we covered it the
la noticia y y lo hemos cubierto la
truth But well for those who don't know the
verdad Pero bueno para el que no sepa la
story Well, a kid a soccer player from
historia Pues un chaval un futbolista de
Córdoba
Córdoba
and what's up Sorry for the delay he was at the
e que lleva Disculpa la demora estaba en
Mother's Day dinner I'll have to
la cena del día de la madre tendré que
see it reuploaded tomorrow there you go kiss
verlo resubido mañana ahí te van beso
Hey what do you think people what do you think of
Oye qué pensáis gente qué pensáis del
this kid who disappeared in
chaval este que ha desaparecido en
Córdoba what do you think of that
Córdoba qué pensáis de ese
kid what do you think of the kid who
chaval qué pensáis del chaval que
disappeared in Córdoba I sincerely I
desapareció en Córdoba yo sinceramente
think I sincerely think that the
yo pienso pienso sinceramente que el
kid is having the best party
chaval se está montando la mejor fiesta
of his life somewhere and he must have seen
de su vida en algún lado y y habrá visto
that that his followers are increasing
que que que le están subiendo los
and everything he must have said [ __ ]
seguidores y todo habrá dicho [__]
Well [ __ ] great you
Pues de [__] madre
know but it's  that he's saying it
sabes pero es que lo está diciendo De
Really
verdad
dude but he's saying it
tío pero es que lo está diciendo De
Really Javier millor is watching you well
verdad Javier millor te está viendo pues
millor if you're watching me I'm sending you a
millor si me estás viendo Te mando un
huge kiss dude
beso enorme tío
and get up here to debate a little bit with me damn Get up
e sube aquí a debatir un dita conmigo
here a little bit
[__] Súbete aquí un dita
with me it's that he comes comes always one
conmigo es que viene viene siempre uno
behind and surpasses the previous one my god
detrás y supera el anterior madre mía
eh but he doesn't I qua that I had
eh pero él no yo me qua que le había
told him like an unfortunate joke Today
dicho como un chiste desafortunado Hoy
is the day what a couple of characters you bring
es el día vaya par de personajes traes
today but the thing is that I thought I had
hoy pero es que yo me creía que le había
told him like an unfortunate joke this one
dicho como un chiste desafortunado este
was gaining followers and it was an
estaba ganando seguidores y era un
unfortunate joke and then I
chiste desafortunado y entonces yo
was saying wow you have to have a
estaba diciendo [__] hay que tener un
little respect because right now there's a
poco de respeto que ahora mismo hay una
family that's there waiting no
familia que está ahí esperando no a la
waiting for no no but the guy is
espera de no no pero el tío te lo está
telling you completely convinced Ah
diciendo completamente convencido Ah
well this one sure this one sure that he has
pues este seguro este seguro que ha
seen this one sure that he has seen eh this one
visto este seguro que ha visto eh este
sure that he has seen that his followers are increasing
seguro que ha visto que le está subiendo
and he said Ah well I
los seguidores y ha dicho Ah pues me
hide I hide I
escondo me
disappear for a week and then I
escondo desaparezco una semana y luego
come back and I have gained 30,000 followers
vuelvo y me han subido 30.000 seguidores
I am famous and and that's it he has  stuck to your
soy famoso y y ya está le ha pegado a tu
mother a heart attack But oh well nothing happens he has
madre un infarto Pero bueno no pasa nada
gained 30,000 followers and that's it I mean but
ha ganado 30.000 seguidores y ya está o
look at what
sea pero fíjate tú lo que está diciendo
the guy is saying yasel a
el colega yasel un
kiss But trust what the guy is saying
beso Pero fíate tú lo que está diciendo
So it seems like a good
O sea que le está pareciendo una buena
idea to disappear for a
idea desaparecer una
week
semana
and no in truth it can happen ch roll this does it
y no en verdad puede pasar ch rollo esto
This one does it on purpose you didn't
lo hace Este sí lo hace queriendo no me
tell me because I already can't
dijisteis porque yo ya esto no me lo
believe that people like that exist no I
puedo creer que existe gente así no O
mean this one does it on purpose
sea este sí lo hace queriendo
eh so that they can funn him no I mean he did
eh para que lo funen no O sea él hacía
this as a joke no The guy like is
esto como gracia no El chaval rollo est
partying in a house such and such And no I think that's why
de fiesta en una casa tal Y no yo creo
the truth because if not what
que por eso la verdad porque si no qué
could happen if not in a
puede pasar si no en una estación de
train station you would do
tren harías
that like If you had imagine
eso en plan Si hubieras imagínate
Imagine I miss a train and I go to
Imagínate yo pierdo un tren y me voy a
a party to a house okay And on such a day
una fiesta a una casa vale Y a al día
I don't know I fall asleep I know all
tal yo que sé me duermo que sé sal todas
the news comes out that I'm missing
las noticias de que estoy desaparecido
Well maybe I'll come up with the idea of
Pues a lo mejor se me ocurre la idea de
continuing to disappear for more days to
seguir desapareciendo más días para
gain a little fame it's  the only thing I
pillar un poco de fama es lo único que
hear
oye
no dude no no no no
no tío no no no no
no but what family member do you have to
no pero con qué familiar te tienes que
sleep with to have a child like that I mean it ca
acostar para tener un hijo así o sea es
n't be a
que no puede ser
dude but how the
tío sea pero cómo
[ __ ] I mean he says but look at what he
[__] o sea dice pero es que fijaros lo
said eh I mean look at what he
que ha dicho eh o sea fijaros lo que ha
said
dicho
and if you if
e si tú
I for example am out there and
si yo por ejemplo estoy por ahí y la
people think I'm missing because I fall
gente me da por desaparecido porque me
asleep or whatever they say no I mean I
duermo o lo que sea dice no O sea me
fall asleep or whatever and when I
duermo o lo que sea y cuando me
wake up to see where you're sleeping
despierto per ver dónde estás dormido
But when I wake up I see that
Pero cuando me despierto veo que está
everyone is talking about me in all
todo el mundo hablando de mí en todos
the media so then I say
los medios pues entonces yo digo
damn how cool the fame no first of all I don't get
[__] qué Guay la fama no ante todo no me
lost a little more Anyway I'm already
pierdo un poco más Total ya estoy
missing because he gives me three more days let's
desaparecido porque me da tres días más
drag this out
que alarguemos la
dude mother of love beautiful
cosa tío madre del amor hermoso
dude mother of love
tío madre del amor
beautiful He was missing a couple of months in
hermoso Le faltaron un par de meses en
the
la
incubator it's just too much
incubadora es que es demasiado
eh it's just too much
eh
even for
es que es demasiado incluso para
anyone saved
cualquiera salvado
Aitana Ah but it's not Aitana
Aitana Ah pero no es la Aitana
eh what did the best guy tell me what are
eh qué me ha dicho el millor que me
you telling me look at the best well
estáis diciendo que mira el millor bueno
Franco this I don't know if he's going to upload the video
Franco esta no sé si va a subir el vídeo
what To leave  or not the best
qué Para irnos o no el millor
and then we'll do the Sleeping Stream at a
y luego haremos el Sleeping Stream a una
more or less inopportune time because Hola
más menos intempestiva porque Hola
España I'll probably do the Sleeping
España seguramente haré el Sleeping
Stream around 9 in the morning in
Stream sobre las 9 de la mañana en
Spain or
España o
so I don't know I feel like spamming games today I do
así no sé me apetece spamear games hoy
n't feel like sleeping so I'll go
no me apetece dormir así que me iré
now for a couple of hours and I can't
ahora un par de horitas y no puedo
rewind And
rebobinar Y
that
eso
Ah what did he
Ah qué ha
say he
dicho
took off the Stream what did he
quitó el Stream qué es lo que
say
dijo
Ah connecting a debate would be good no a
Ah conectar un debate estaría bien no un
bat a debate has to be a
murciélago un debate tiene que ser una
gem right I haven't paused it yet
joyita verdad no lo he pausado aún
featured
destacado
recent
reciente
recent the broadcasts are not showing
reciente no salen las emisiones
a debate has to be a gem
un debate tiene que ser una jollita
right I
verdad
paused but
pause pero
not let's see if there's any
no a ver si hay algún
click it doesn't let click or It leaves anything why does
click no deja click ni Deja nada por qué
Wonder take it off a
quita Wonder un
kiss he said bitter For talking all
beso te dijo amargado Por hablar todo el
day I
día salseo
practically gossip oh my god
prácticamente madre mía
yes the gameover he the best has for
sí el gameover el el millor tiene para
Game Over yes the best has for Game
Game Over sí el millor tiene para Game
Over I know guys well I'm going
Over Ya lo sé chicos pues me voy que
Fran I think Fran won't
Fran yo creo que ya Fran no
upload or I think
subirá o yo creo que
Fran wait I'm going to go to Fran's Twitter
Fran se espérate voy a ir al Twitter de
I think Francis hasn't uploaded anything
yo creo que Francis no ha subido nada
yet it must
todavía tiene que
be that he's gone so crazy
ser que se le ha ido tantísimo la olla
in the  video that he's thinking about it doesn't
en el vídeo que que se lo está pensando
stop Game not verd the best eh 100%
no para Game no verd el millor eh 100%
What happens is that you would have to have
Lo que pasa que eso habría que tener
a lot of patience eh
muchísima paciencia eh
an It's
an
been a long time since you did a good Game
Ya hace mucho que no haces un buen Game
Over Well don't believe it Eh that I'm not
Over Pues no te creas Eh que no me
lacking in desire eh There's
faltan ganas eh Hay
one that I can't talk about yet
alguno del que no puedo hablar todavía
but maybe in a few months
pero a lo mejor en unos meses
Ugh
Uf
guys I'm going to Mimí
chicos me voy a Mimí
okay I'm going to mimir
vale me voy a mimir
guys I'm going to mimir because tomorrow I start
chicos me voy a mimir que mañana empiezo
training tomorrow the
el entrenamiento mañana viene el
personal trainer is coming again I want
entrenador personal ya de nuevo quiero
one quad a
uno cuad un
kiss
beso
eh guys Thank you very much to all for the little
eh chicos Muchas gracias a todos por el
guide we're back at it
directillo ya estamos de vuelta a saco
now at it's best but tremendously
ya a saco pero a saco tremendamente
and at full throttle Okay See you guys and the
y y a tope Vale Nos vemos chicos e la
logic of El moror is terrible as if a
lógica de El moror es pésima como si un
hanged man with CPR couldn't stay alive
ahorcado con rcp no quedase vivo lavados
stomach pumps didn't exist what a
de estómago no existieran vaya
character no comment guys go
personaje sin comentario chicos a
rest a kiss I love you
descansar un beso os quiero
[Music]
[Música]
very handsome
guapísimos